

<dir>
  <title>Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D</title>
  <summary>Storyline
After the Battle of New York, the world has changed. It now knows not only about the Avengers, but also the powerful menaces that require those superheroes and more to face them. In response, Phil Coulson of the Strategic Homeland Intervention, Enforcement and Logistics Division assembles an elite covert team to find and deal with these threats wherever they are found. With a world rapidly becoming more bizarre and dangerous than ever before as the supervillains arise, these agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. are ready to take them on.
12 | 45min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/agentsofshield.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTc5NzEzMzA2MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDkyNzgyNDM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3NTIxNTYzN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTIyNzE1OQ@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>American Housewife</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A family comedy narrated by Katie, a strong-willed mother, raising her flawed family in a wealthy town filled with perfect wives and their perfect offspring.
30min | Comedy | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/americanhousewife.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZWNjZTBiMGEtMWFmYi00M2EwLWE2NjMtNTI2NGYzNGI5Yjc2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzAzNTY3MDM@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTEzMDU2Mzc2OTJeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDI5MTE1OTkx._V1_SY1000_SX750_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Animal Kingdom</title>
  <summary>Storyline
The series centers on 17-year-old Joshua "J" Cody, who moves in with his freewheeling relatives in their Southern California beach town after his mother dies of a heroin overdose. Headed by boot-tough matriarch Janine "Smurf" Cody and her right-hand Baz, who runs the business and calls the shots, the clan also consists of Pope, the oldest and most dangerous of the Cody boys; Craig, the tough and fearless middle son; and Deran, the troubled, suspicious "baby" of the family.
15 | 1h | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/animalkingdom.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZjk2ZWVkODItOTIyZi00M2M5LWFkZjctMzI5NzMzZWJhODY4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODQyNDU2MTU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjc4M2M2ZmMtYjQwYy00MzkwLWE4ZTAtZGQ5NTMwOGE5OTgxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDU4Njg2MzM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Altered Carbon</title>
<summary>Storyline
ALTERED CARBON is set in a future where consciousness is digitized and stored in cortical stacks implanted in the spine, allowing humans to survive physical death by having their memories and consciousness "re-sleeved" into new bodies. The story follows specially trained "Envoy" soldier Takeshi Kovacs, who is downloaded from an off-world prison and into a combat ready sleeve at the behest of Laurens Bancroft, a highly influential aristocrat. Bancroft was killed, and the last automatic backup of his stack was made hours before his death, leaving him with no memory of who killed him and why. While police ruled it a suicide, Bancroft is convinced he was murdered and wants Kovacs to find out the truth.
18 | 1h | Drama, Sci-Fi, Thriller | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/alteredcarbon.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjQyOTE4NjE0M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzcxMzY1NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNWI2OGE1MDItNTc1Zi00YTE3LTgwYmUtYTBjMzlkYTI1ODVhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODExNTExMTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>American Gods</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  A recently released ex-convict named Shadow meets a mysterious man who calls himself "Wednesday" and who knows more than he first seems to about Shadow's life and past.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/americangods.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY2NTUwNjUxMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzIxNzE5NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BY2U1M2Q4OGEtYzg0OC00Nzk1LTk5MjItZTI1OTEyYzdlNjQyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjAwNTYwNDg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1761,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>American Horror Story</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Both physical and psychological horrors affect a decomposing family, workers and residents of an insane asylum, a coven of witches, a cast of circus freaks, the employees and guests at a struggling hotel, a family who moved into a mysterious farmhouse, and the members of a small suburb in Michigan in this haunting anthology series, focusing on the themes of infidelity, sanity, oppression, discrimination, addiction, and exploitation.
18 | 1h | Drama, Horror, Thriller | TV Series (2011– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/americanhorrorstory.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjQ2MjA4MDM1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzA3MDgzMzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,761,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWVhZTU5MjYtNjc5Yi00NGY4LWFjMjUtN2U2ZGUyMGU0MjFhL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTYyMTYyMzM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Arrested Development</title>
  <summary>StorylineMeet the wildly dysfunctional Bluth family. This family was once at the height of real estate development in Orange County, California. But when the family business - the Bluth Company - goes bust, they're suddenly found penniless with their assets frozen. They move into their last remaining asset - the model home left over from their latest housing tract. Their luxury vehicles are replaced with a reminder of the family's former wealth: 'the stair car that accompanied their private jet'. The patriarch of the family is George Bluth - he's now in prison, and loving every minute of it. His wife Lucille and daughter Lindsay are spoiled socialites who can't handle getting kicked out of family restaurants. His son Buster is in his mid 30's and lives at home. His son George Oscar Bluth is a magician who started a group to get magicians to be taken seriously, and gets kicked out when his own tricks are revealed. Lindsay is married to a man named Tobias Funke, once a psychiatrist, who decides to become an actor. The only sane member of the family: Michael Bluth, along with his son George Michael, want nothing to do with the family business. But one bizarre circumstance after another keeps Michael and George Michael from leaving their eccentric family.
  12 | 22min | Comedy | TV Series (2003– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/arresteddevelopment.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA4NjUzNTk4NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODI1OTY0NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTNjMDE0YTktYWYzOS00YmYzLWIzNjEtZTcwZjk4ZDA1MWY5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTgyNDM1OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1447,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Arrow</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Oliver Queen and his father are lost at sea when their luxury yacht sinks, apparently in a storm. His father dies, but Oliver survives for five years on an uncharted island and eventually returns home. But he wasn't alone on the island where he learned not only how to fight and survive but also of his father's corruption and unscrupulous business dealings. He returns to civilization a changed man, determined to put things right. He disguises himself with the hood of one of his mysterious island mentors, arms himself with a bow and sets about hunting down the men and women who have corrupted his city.
15 | 42min | Action, Adventure, Crime | TV Series (2012– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/arrow.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUwOTgyNTQ1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDEyNzM3MzI@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZDczMjIyOWQtMDYyMS00Njc5LThlZDItMWRhMjhlZjExMDUzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjkzNjQzODI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Archer</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Covert black ops and espionage take a back seat to zany personalities and relationships between secret agents and drones.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/archer.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3NTMwMzY2OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDcxMjQ0NDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjY4MjM5MmYtODk2ZS00NDJjLThiY2EtY2I0NDI1YzZmNjU1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTMxMTA0NjY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Atlanta</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Based in Atlanta, Earn and his cousin Alfred are trying to make their way up in the world through the rap scene. Along the way they come face to face with social and economic issues touching on race, relationships, poverty, status and parenthood.
30min | Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/atlanta.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUyMjQ0NzM2Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjM1NjU0OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjQyMjEzOTg0N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODc5MDg2OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1776,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Atypical</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Atypical is a coming of age story that follows Sam, an 18-year-old on the autistic spectrum as he searches for love and independence. While Sam is on his funny yet emotional journey of self-discovery, the rest of his family must grapple with change in their own lives as they all struggle with the central theme: what does it really mean to be normal?
15 | 30min | Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/atypical.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTcyNzk3MzM2OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODcwMzYxNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU0MTE2MzI2NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODk5MzIxNjM@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Band of Brothers</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  The story of Easy Company of the U.S. Army 101st Airborne Division, and their mission in World War II Europe, from Operation Overlord, through V-J Day.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/bandofbrothers.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTI3ODc2ODc0M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwMjgzNjc3._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BY2E0M2UyNjQtNWQyNC00MDdjLTk5MzMtMDUwOGQ1OTI2YzRiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzM5ODEzMDY@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Batman </title>
  <summary>Storyline
  A young Bruce Wayne is in his third year of trying to establish himself as Batman, protector of Gotham City. Living in Gotham, a metropolis where shadows run long and deep, beneath elevated train tracks, this younger Batman will confront each of his familiar foes for the first time.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/thebatman.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjE2MzA0YTgtNjQ3MS00MjMxLWE2MzMtOGYzMTZjZjFiYTI0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTgwMzk1MTA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://static1.squarespace.com/static/51b3dc8ee4b051b96ceb10de/t/5b555fea8a922d868e02c3f7/1532321776466/batman-the-animated-series-will-be-released-on-blu-ray-in-october-social.jpg?format=2500w</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Billions</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Billions is a complex drama about power politics in the world of New York high finance. Shrewd, savvy U.S. Attorney Chuck Rhoades and the brilliant, ambitious hedge fund king Bobby "Axe" Axelrod are on an explosive collision course, with each using all of his considerable smarts, power and influence to outmaneuver the other. The stakes are in the billions in this timely, provocative series.
15 | 1h | Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/billions.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDQ3OTMyMzM5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTA2NzU2NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzc5Y2EyYWEtOTI5Yi00ZmI5LWI3ZTMtOGM3YjVhZWZkMWE5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjY3NjAyNTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Black Lightning</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Jefferson Pierce has made his choice. He hung up the suit and his secret identity years ago, but with a daughter hell-bent on justice and a star student being recruited by a local gang, he'll be pulled back into the fight as the wanted vigilante and DC legend: Black Lightning.
15 | 43min | Action , Drama , Sci-Fi | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/blacklightning.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3NTk5Mzg5OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDgyMjQyNjM@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDYxYzRhZjUtZjBjZC00YjE1LThlNDItOGQ3NTEzZjg3ZDAxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODM2NzY3Mjg@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Black Mirror</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  An anthology series exploring a twisted, high-tech world where humanity's greatest innovations and darkest instincts collide.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/blackmirror.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTEwYzNiMGUtNzRlYS00MTMzLTliNzgtOGUxZGZiNThlNWYwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDc5MTk0NzA2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzcxNzk0NDM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Blindspot</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A woman with no memories of her past (Jane Doe), is found naked in Times Square with her body fully covered in intricate tattoos. Her discovery sets off a vast and complex mystery that immediately ignites the attention of the FBI, which begins to follow the road map of her tattoos into a larger conspiracy of crime, while bringing her closer to discovering the truth about her identity.
42min | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/blindspot.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjJiOGM3NmQtYzEwNS00ZTgyLWI2NTYtZGZmYjNmZjAzYTExXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxOTg0ODQxNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDc5MTY3OTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Blue Bloods</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Blue Bloods follows the lives of the NYPD's First Family of Law Enforcement: the Reagans. Frank, the Police Comissioner and son of former PC Henry Reagan, must balance his duties of running the largest police force in the world and being his kids' boss. His daughter Erin is an Assistant District Attorney, son Danny is a senior detective and fellow Marine Veteran, and new Harvard Law grad turned cop, Jamie all swirl through this family drama and passionately defend their city from harm. The Irish-American family is deeply rooted in their patriotism, passion, and love of family.
15 | 43min | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2010– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/bluebloods.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjY0NTE1ODU3OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTI4NDQwMDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTMxMjUyNDUxOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjkyNTk4Mw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Bloodline</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  A family of adult siblings find that their past secrets and scars are revealed when their black sheep of a brother returns home.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/bloodline.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTU4OTY0MzM1OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjkxMzE0MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,704,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmNkNDEzYTgtMmQ4MC00MDY2LTlmZDAtYTAxMmUwMDMwN2EwL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTE4MTk1MzM@._V1_SY1000_SX1500_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Breaking Bad</title>
  <summary>Storyline
When chemistry teacher Walter White is diagnosed with Stage III cancer and given only two years to live, he decides he has nothing to lose. He lives with his teenage son, who has cerebral palsy, and his wife, in New Mexico. Determined to ensure that his family will have a secure future, Walt embarks on a career of drugs and crime. He proves to be remarkably proficient in this new world as he begins manufacturing and selling methamphetamine with one of his former students. The series tracks the impacts of a fatal diagnosis on a regular, hard working man, and explores how a fatal diagnosis affects his morality and transforms him into a major player of the drug trade.
18 | 49min | Crime, Drama, Thriller | TV Series (2008–2013)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/breakingbad.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZDNhNzhkNDctOTlmOS00NWNmLWEyODQtNWMxM2UzYmJiNGMyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTMxMjgxMzA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTEwMDhmNmUtNGJmNi00NGUwLTkxOWQtNzI1NDUwZTFkMThkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg0Nzk2Nzc@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Broadchurch</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  The murder of a young boy in a small coastal town brings a media frenzy, which threatens to tear the community apart.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/broadchurch.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWRmYjVjM2YtNDAwMi00ZGZmLTgzMjQtYjY4MTNjMTljNjhjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjExMjk0ODk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,708,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4OTAwNTczOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTM0OTY2NDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1444,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Bob's Burgers </title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Bob Belcher, along with his wife and 3 children, try to run their last hope of holding the family together, which is running Bob's dream restaurant.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/bobsburgers.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGJiNmM1NDctNWUxYS00YzE4LWJjNTgtYTJhYzE0NjFmMTMwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjBjYTAzMTYtNWExNS00OTkyLTgwZTItZjAxY2Y5MDZlNTYzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODI1OTI4OTk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Brooklyn Nine - Nine</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Captain Ray Holt takes over Brooklyn's 99th precinct, which includes Detective Jake Peralta, a talented but carefree detective who's used to doing whatever he wants. The other employees of the 99th precinct include Detective Amy Santiago, Jake's over achieving and competitive partner; Detective Rosa Diaz, a tough and kept to herself coworker; Detective Charles Boyle, Jake's best friend who also has crush on Rosa; Detective Sergeant Terry Jeffords, who was recently taken off the field after the birth of his twin girls; and Gina Linetti, the precinct's sarcastic administrator.
12 | 22min | Comedy, Crime | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/brooklynninenine.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDc3NzQxODAwOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODkwMjU2MzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZWQwZjExZjAtM2I2OS00NzFiLTlmNjUtNmZlOGUzMWJjYjk0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc5NTc1MTg@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Ballers</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Ballers is a half-hour comedy series starring Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson. Looking at the lives of former and current football players, the show follows former superstar Spencer Strasmore as he gets his life on track in retirement while mentoring other current and former players through the daily grind of the business of football.
15 | 30min | Comedy, Drama, Sport | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/ballers.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTIzMDk3Mzc4Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODExNDAwNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkwMjM3MTkzMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzA2MTEwNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Banshee</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Lucas Hood, an ex-con and master thief, assumes the identity of a murdered sheriff where he continues his criminal activities. His past seems to haunt him by those he betrayed years earlier. This ex-con imposes his own brand of justice where violence erupts at every turn in the not so quiet Amish town of Banshee, Pennsylvania.
18 | 1h | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2013–2016)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/banshee.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkzNTA1MDI5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTY3NjAwOQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWMwMTE3YjktNzQxZC00Yzc4LTk5YmUtYTAzOTBmMWNmYTEyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Barry</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A hit man from the Midwest moves to Los Angeles and gets caught up in the city's theatre arts scene.
30min | Comedy | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/barry.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjQyNDk0NTIyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTQ2Nzg4NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzA1MDc4YTItZDViNS00MWRlLWFkZDAtZjlmYmY4ODcwZDgzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg0Nzk2Nzc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Better Call Saul</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Before Saul Goodman, he was Jimmy McGill. And if you're calling Jimmy, you're in real trouble. The prequel to "Breaking Bad" follows small-time attorney Jimmy McGill as he transforms into Walter White's morally challenged lawyer, Saul Goodman.
15 | 46min | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/bettercallsaul.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTAxOTQ0MjUzMzJeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDY0NTAxNzMx._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE1MTcwOTk2OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzQ0MzI2NzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>BoJack Horseman</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  BoJack Horseman was the star of the hit TV show "Horsin' Around" in the '90s, now he's washed up, living in Hollywood, complaining about everything, and wearing colorful sweaters.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/bojackthehorseman.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzgzNzg3MDkyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTk5MjAzNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODJhNjljOTUtMTBmOS00NTFjLTgyY2EtMTJhMGQ5YzY1YWM5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA2NzkwNTc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Castle Rock</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A psychological-horror series set in the Stephen King multiverse, Castle Rock combines the mythological scale and intimate character storytelling of King's best-loved works, weaving an epic saga of darkness and light, played out on a few square miles of Maine woodland. The fictional Maine town of Castle Rock has figured prominently in King's literary career: Cujo, The Dark Half, IT and Needful Things, as well as novella The Body and numerous short stories such as Rita Hayworth and The Shawshank Redemption are either set there or contain references to Castle Rock. Castle Rock is an original suspense/thriller - a first-of-its-kind reimagining that explores the themes and worlds uniting the entire King canon, while brushing up against some of his most iconic and beloved stories.
1h | Drama, Fantasy, Horror | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/castlerock.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMzMDYxNzA3MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDAzNDQ4NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzFjYTEwNjUtMjAyMS00OTBhLTk2YTctYjM4MjEzNjE1OWU3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTg4OTMzNjQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Casual</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A new comedy series about a bachelor brother and his newly divorced sister living under one roof again. Together, they coach each other through the crazy world of dating while raising her teenage daughter.
15 | 25min | Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/casual.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjQ1MzQzNDA1MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjgzNjE5NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDQ2ZjM1MTUtYmM1Zi00NmEzLWE2YjMtOGNlYmQzMDkyNDRjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDI0MTYyNzU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Chicago Fire</title>
  <summary>Storyline
The story of firefighters in Chicago, both on a personal and professional level.
43min | Action, Drama | TV Series (2012– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/chicagofire.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzBiYWVjMjgtMTUzYy00YTFlLWE2OWYtMzY3ZmNmYTE0ODg5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTkwOTM0MjA2Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDk1MTI4MjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Chicago Med</title>
  <summary>Storyline
An emotional thrill ride through the day-to-day chaos of the city's most explosive hospital and the courageous team of doctors who hold it together. They will tackle unique new cases inspired by topical events, forging fiery relationships in the pulse-pounding pandemonium of the emergency room.
15 | 43min | Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/chicagomed.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTdhNWI4N2YtN2NmNC00NTljLThjMzQtOGYyYjBlMDAwYjljXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDYyOTUyMzUyOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTY1MjI5NjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Chicago P.D</title>
  <summary>Storyline
District 21 of the Chicago Police Department is made up of two distinctly different groups. There are the uniformed cops who patrol the beat and go head-to-head with the city's street crimes. And there's the Intelligence Unit, the team that combats the city's major offenses - organized crime, drug trafficking, high profile murders and beyond.
43min | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2014– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/chicagopd.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNWFkYzFmMzctNDMzOS00ZDlkLWIwOGUtYWI1MTkyZDI1MThkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ0NzQ2MDI1NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTA1OTEwMTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Chilling Adventures of Sabrina</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Reimagines the origin and adventures of Sabrina: the Teenage Witch as a dark coming-of-age story that traffics in horror, the occult and, of course, witchcraft. Tonally in the vein of Rosemary's Baby and The Exorcist, this adaptation finds Sabrina Spellman wrestling to reconcile her dual nature - half-witch, half-mortal - while standing against the evil forces that threaten her, her family and the daylight world humans inhabit.
15 | 1h | Drama , Fantasy , Horror | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/chillingadventuresofsabrina.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTQyMDYwNDMyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjM4NTIzNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGRiMjk3N2MtYjE3Yi00NGU5LTljYWUtMmM3NjBmZDIyMmJhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODAzMDY0MTY@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Cloak & Dagger </title>
  <summary>Storyline
Tandy Bowen and Tyrone Johnson, two teenagers from different backgrounds, acquire superpowers while forming a romantic relationship. They soon realize that their powers work better when they are together, but their feelings for each other make their already complicated world even more challenging.
44min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/cloakanddagger.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2NiODhhY2UtNDMzNy00YWYzLTk0NGYtZDk5MjQyOTE0ZmFmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc4MjczMTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjUxNjgxZmUtOTI2Zi00NTc3LWExMDMtYmEwNGM4MDk1MjYxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQ2NDE1OTk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Cobra Kai</title>
<summary>Storyline
Thirty years after their final confrontation at the 1984 All Valley Karate Tournament, Johnny Lawrence is at rock-bottom as an unemployed handyman haunted by his wasted life. However, when Johnny rescues a bullied kid, Miguel, from bullies, he is inspired to restart the notorious Cobra Kai dojo. However, this revitalization of his life and related misunderstandings find Johnny restarting his old rivalry with Daniel LaRousso, a successful businessman who may be happily married, but is missing an essential balance in life since the death of his mentor, Mr. Miyagi. Meanwhile, even as this antipathy festers, it finds itself reflected in their protegees as Miguel and his comrades are gradually poisoned by Cobra Kai's thuggish philosophy. Meanwhile, while Daniel's daughter, Samantha, finds herself in the middle of this conflict amidst false friends, Johnny's estranged miscreant son, Robby, finds himself inadvertently coming under Daniel's wing and flourishes in ways worthy of Mr. Miyagi.
30min | Action, Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/cobrakai.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzZlYzFkMGYtZmE1Ni00MWFkLTkxNzYtZTc3MjZhYWRhZDgxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMDA4NzMyOA@@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjUwNzExMTU2Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTM0Nzc4NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1499,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Code Black</title>
  <summary>Storyline
This show is based on the award-winning documentary of the same name. This medical drama follows the staff in an extremely busy emergency room as they cope with a staggering amount of patients, which oftentimes outweighs the hospital's resources, resulting in a code black.
42min | Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/codeblack.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5NjY2OTk5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODU4NDQwMDI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjAxNDI3NzU2MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjI1MjY5NjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Colony</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Set in the near future, Colony centers on a family who must make difficult decisions as they balance staying together while trying to survive. They live in L.A., which has been occupied by a force of outside intruders. While some people have chosen to collaborate with the authorities and benefit from the new order, others have rebelled and suffer the consequences.
42min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/colony.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg1MzAzODQ5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDA1MDI0NTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA2NzA4NjYzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTkwOTY5MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1545,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Condor</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Based on the novel "Six Days of the Condor" by James Grady and screenplay "Three Days of the Condor" by Lorenzo Semple Jr. and David Rayfiel, CONDOR follows CIA analyst Joe Turner who stumbles onto a plan that threatens the lives of millions. Joe has always been conflicted about his work for the CIA. But when something he's discovered gets his entire office killed, leaving Joe as the only survivor and forcing him to go on the run, the theoretical reservations he's harbored turn into all-too-real moral dilemmas. Under pressure, Joe will be forced to redefine who he is and what he's capable of in order to discover the truth and to stop a plot that threatens the lives of millions.
1h | Thriller | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/condor.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYmFhOGYyNzQtYzlmYS00ZjkyLWJlNzQtMWU3MTk2MWFjOGRmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,697,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTc2MzM5MTEtOTc1OC00OTRlLWE4OTQtODUwYTJjZDEyYTQzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODUyMDgyOTU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Crazy Ex-Girlfriend</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  To most looking in, Rebecca Bunch has a great life: a high powered job as an attorney in a prestigious New York law firm, great future prospects in her chosen profession, looks, brains, and money. But she has always suffered from anxiety and depression, for which she is on a plethora of pills. Those maladies are largely from being pushed by her overbearing Jewish mother, which also led to Rebecca's father abandoning the family when she was young. When on the streets of New York Rebecca runs into Josh Chan, her boyfriend from summer camp ten years ago when they were sixteen, she remembers back to that time as the happiest time in her life, happiness which eludes her. When Josh mentions that he is imminently moving back to his hometown of West Covina, California, Rebecca decides to pursue happiness in moving to West Covina herself, telling people it's because she got a fabulous job there, where in reality it's to rekindle a relationship with Josh, which she believes is what will make her happy. As Rebecca ekes out a life in West Covina with a wide array of new friends, colleagues, allies and enemies - within this collection being Josh and his friends - Rebecca may come to some realizations about her life and what she is trying to achieve. Does this all make her a crazy ex-girlfriend, or is it a little more nuanced than that?
  42min | Comedy, Musical | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/crazyexgirlfriend.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzU3ODQxMjgzOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDg4NDgzMDI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY4NTA2ODgyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTg1NzYwNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Criminal Minds</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Based in Quantico, Virginia, the Behavioral Analysis Unit (BAU) is a subsection of the FBI. Called in by local police departments to assist in solving crimes of a serial and/or extremely violent nature where the perpetrator is unknown (referred to by the Unit as the unknown subject or unsub for short), the BAU uses the controversial scientific art of profiling to track and apprehend the unsub. Profiling entails coming up with basic characteristics of the unsub and the victims (referred to as the victimology), using evidence from the case and matching that information to historic precedents and psychological analyses as a means to solve the case. Because of the nature of the work conducted by the BAU - the work being time consuming and psychologically demanding - its members are fiercely loyal to the Unit and to its other members. Also because of the work's overall demanding nature, not many members of the BAU have been able to maintain a happy or stable family life.
42min | Crime , Drama , Mystery | TV Series (2005– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/criminalminds.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNGE2ZmFkZTYtNjRiOS00ZjE3LThjOWMtZTViZjRmNDFjNTQwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzAyOTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIxMzY3Nzk1OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDAxNjgwNA@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Community</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  A suspended lawyer is forced to enroll in a community college with an eclectic staff and student body.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/community.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ2Njk2MzY2M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDkxODg3MDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjZmMTA4OTMtMTdkNy00MjA0LWIyNjItODg4NTRkMGJiNzdmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjUxMjc1OTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Dark</title>
  <summary>Storyline
   A family saga with a supernatural twist, set in a German town, where the disappearance of two young children exposes the relationships among four families.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/dark.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUzNjQ2MTY5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTAzNTQxNDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzg0ZDA5OTItYjM2OC00Yzc4LWEyZWQtOGRlMmE1ZjI4NzVkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTAyODA2MDg@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Dark Matter</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  In the dystopian 27th century, six people wake up on a deserted spaceship with no memory of who they are or what they're doing there. They reluctantly team up and set off to find answers with the help of a female android.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/darkmatters.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjI5OGMxNzYtZmZiYS00NDI1LWI4NWMtOTZmNjY1MjMzZjExXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTgxMjE3OTQ@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmEwNDdmZDQtZmE3My00ODNkLTg3NzQtYzc2ZGY4YTMzODNhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc5Mjg0NjU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Daredevil</title>
  <summary>Storyline
As a child Matt Murdock was blinded by a chemical spill in a freak accident. Instead of limiting him it gave him superhuman senses that enabled him to see the world in a unique and powerful way. Now he uses these powers to deliver justice, not only as a lawyer in his own law firm, but also as vigilante at night, stalking the streets of Hell's Kitchen as Daredevil, the man without fear.
18 | 54min | Action , Crime , Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/daredevil.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODcwOTg2MDE3NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTUyNTY1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgyOTAzMjAxMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDI3OTkwNTE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,525_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Deception</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A superstar magician Cameron Black whose career is ruined by scandal has only one place to turn to practice his art of deception, illusion, and influence, the FBI where he'll become the world's first consulting illusionist, helping the government solve crimes that defy explanation, and trap criminals and spies by using deception.
41min | Drama | TV Series (2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/deception.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BN2RlMDVlZTktMjQxNy00YjdjLTlmMWYtNDUwMDZkNjE4ODJmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjU0OTAwMDc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzUxZjBmNTItYWM3OC00ODI5LTkwYmYtNTc5YzI3NDE2OTJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjkwOTAyMDU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1492,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Dexter</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  By day, mild-mannered Dexter is a blood-spatter analyst for the Miami police. But at night, he is a serial killer who only targets other murderers.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/dexter.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTM5MjkwMTI0MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODQwMTc0OQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzYxMDAxMDEyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjEwNDg3OA@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Deep State</title>
  <summary>Storyline
What happens when a man who believes he has retired from MI6 is called back to do one more job to regain his life, only to discover that this job may mean he has no life to go back to.
45min | Action, Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/deepstate.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYzdiNmJhNDYtYTgwZC00NWVlLWEyMjItMDIyOGMzMWVjNjRiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYzdiNmJhNDYtYTgwZC00NWVlLWEyMjItMDIyOGMzMWVjNjRiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Designated Survivor</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Kiefer Sutherland stars as Tom Kirkman, a lower-level cabinet member who is suddenly appointed President of the United States after a catastrophic attack on the US Capitol during the State of the Union, on the highly anticipated series Designated Survivor. In this dramatic thriller, Kirkman will struggle to keep the country and his own family from falling apart, while navigating the highly-volatile political arena and while leading the search to find who is responsible for the attack.
1h | Action, Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2016–2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/designatedsurvivor.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjUxODc2NTIxMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjgxMDkyMzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjQ1MTY3Mjg2OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDE3ODQ3OTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir> 

<dir>
  <title>Doctor Who</title>
  <summary>Storyline
The Doctor, a Time Lord from the race whose home planet is Gallifrey, travels through time and space in his/her ship the TARDIS (an acronym for Time and Relative Dimension In Space) with numerous companions. From time to time he/she regenerates into a new form (which is how the series has been running since the departure of the original actor, William Hartnell, in 1966).
12 | 45min | Adventure , Drama , Family | TV Series (2005– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/doctorwho.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDY1YmZhZjEtY2E3NC00M2VkLThlZmUtODczMmNiZjMxMWRhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzA5NTYxMDg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,720,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTFmODVlNzEtNzZjMS00MDc3LTk1MWEtZmY5MWMwYzliZTI3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQ0MzA0NTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Dynasty</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Follows two of America's wealthiest families as they feud for control over their fortune and their children.
12 | 42min | Drama | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/dynasty.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTlmMDRmOTMtMmQ0Mi00YjAzLWFlZDMtNTJjODQyOGE1ZTk5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZmM1NGQ1OWUtY2FmNC00MzUyLTg5MjAtZWYzZjJjOGUxYzRjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzc1Njg4NTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>El Chapo</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A look at the life of notorious drug kingpin, El Chapo, from his early days in the 1980s working for the Guadalajara Cartel, to his rise to power of during the '90s and his ultimate downfall in 2016.
15 | 43min | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/elchapo.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzE5ZjVkMTItYjllNi00YThiLThhMzAtM2NkNTlkNmY1NWJmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzdiZGU2MDMtODViOS00YmExLWExNmUtMDJlMzMzZTUyNTdjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjE0MDE2MTU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Empire</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Lucious, the founder and CEO of a successful record label has been diagnosed with ALS. He must choose one of his three sons to take over the company when he dies. Meanwhile, his ex wife and co-founder, Cookie, has been released from prison and wants to reclaim her rightful place in the company.
42min | Drama, Music | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/empire.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTk0MjI5MzI5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDMwNDM5NDM@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYzNiNGIzNTctYWQwNC00ODI0LTg4M2QtNTZiMmVmYWNlZGYzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc5Nzc4MDY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Entourage </title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Film star Vince Chase navigates the vapid terrain of Los Angeles with a close circle of friends and his trusty agent.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/entourage.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDg3ZDc2MDQtNzQwZi00YzFjLTgyOTMtMDMzZTc5N2VlNTg2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTMyOTMwMzkyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzg5NzE2Ng@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1502,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Fargo</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Various chronicles of deception, intrigue and murder in and around frozen Minnesota. Yet all of these tales mysteriously lead back one way or another to Fargo, North Dakota.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/fargo.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5NTYxNjkyNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzY1Mjg4MTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzkxMmE1ZjktNmRmMS00ZWJlLTgyMDEtMGJlZWQyNTRmZjU2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzg5MjYxOTU@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,881_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Family Guy</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Sick, twisted and politically incorrect, the animated series features the adventures of the Griffin family. Endearingly ignorant Peter and his stay-at-home wife Lois reside in Quahog, R.I., and have three kids. Meg, the eldest child, is a social outcast, and teenage Chris is awkward and clueless when it comes to the opposite sex. The youngest, Stewie, is a genius baby bent on killing his mother and destroying the world. The talking dog, Brian, keeps Stewie in check while sipping martinis and sorting through his own life issues.
15 | 22min | Animation, Comedy | TV Series (1998– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/familyguy.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNGRkMTllZTUtZTQyYi00NjVlLTlhZjEtODExNjQ4YjQ1Y2RjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTZiMGMwMGEtNGNmNy00M2ViLTgyZTItNWJhODFlZDc4YWNlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_SY999_SX1776_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>FBI</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Procedural drama about the inner workings of the New York office of the FBI, bringing to bear all the Bureau's skills, intellect and mind-blowing technology to keep New York and the country safe.
1h | Crime , Drama , Mystery | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/fbi.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg5Mjg5NDk4OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjY1ODIyNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,686,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmI4NjQzNmUtYmE0OS00M2ZkLTk3Y2YtZDY1MmZmY2ExYzJiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTExNDQ2MTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Fear The Walking Dead</title>
<summary>Storyline
Spin off series of The Walking Dead that portrays the beginning events of the zombie apocalypse in the West coast during the same time frame when the city of Atlanta was falling under attack, while Rick was in a coma at the local hospital. It shows how the strain was already in full effect in the south while it's just starting in California.
44min | Drama, Horror, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/fearthewalkingdead.xml</link>
 <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTU0NzUxNTA0Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzQxMTc1ODE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTU3OTgyNzEyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzE3ODQxNTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Friends</title>
<summary>Storyline
Follows the personal and professional lives of six twenty to thirty-something-year-old friends living in Manhattan.
</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/friends.xml</link>
 <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDI2ODYyYjItMzAwMy00MmMxLWE4ZTQtOWM0NDI5ODMwZmQyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmZmOTQ0NjgtNTI4OS00MWEzLTk3Y2ItNmVlNWY1Njc2MzYxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODY0NzcxNw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Futurama</title>
<summary>Storyline
Philip J. Fry, a pizza guy, is accidentally frozen in 1999 and thawed out New Year's Eve 2999.
</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/futurama.xml</link>
 <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzA2ZDk2ZTUtMWU2Yi00NDVmLTk1ODEtMmFmMjQyNWYzODI0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,650,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYTdmMWU4ZDEtY2Q0Mi00NWFiLWJlYmMtZjhmMzFlNWExMzg3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Game of Thrones</title>
  <summary>Storyline
In the mythical continent of Westeros, several powerful families fight for control of the Seven Kingdoms. As conflict erupts in the kingdoms of men, an ancient enemy rises once again to threaten them all. Meanwhile, the last heirs of a recently usurped dynasty plot to take back their homeland from across the Narrow Sea.
18 | 57min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2011– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/gameofthrones.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE3NTQ1NDg1Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzY2NDA0MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTQwNjczNTc5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDA3MTcyNg@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Genius</title>
  <summary>Storyline
The life stories of history's greatest minds. From their days as young adults to their final years we see their discoveries, loves, relationships, causes, flaws and genius.
43min | Biography, Drama, History | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/genius.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjMxNTMxNDMxNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTk3NDUyNTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZjE2YjYyMGYtMTkwNC00ZThlLThjMTQtYzU4MjM3M2QyNWVjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzQ3MDU1Mzc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Ghosted</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Described as a sort of comedic X-Files, Ghosted centers on Leroy Wright, a cynical, hilarious skeptic, and Max Allison, a genius "true believer" in the paranormal, who are hired by the Underground Investigative Service to look into the rampant "unexplained" activity in Los Angeles - all while uncovering a larger mystery that could threaten the existence of the human race.
30min | Comedy, Fantasy, Horror | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/ghosted.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODMxMDkxMDg2MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjc5MjU5MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,646,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjVlNWUyZjAtZmUyOS00OTU3LTg5YWEtN2Q3NDc5NjI2NTRiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjEwNTM2Mzc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1497,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Ghoul</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A prisoner arrives at a remote military interrogation centre and turns the tables on his interrogators, exposing their most shameful secrets.
45min | Horror | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/ghoul.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjAyMDMzNTU5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjg2NjExNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjU5ODg5ZTItMmEwNy00YzhiLThlZjQtNGUwOWVmNTJhMWU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDMxOTA5OTY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Gomorra: La serie </title>
<meta>
<summary>Storyline
Ciro disregards tradition in his attempt to become the next boss of his crime syndicate. The internal power struggle puts him and his entire family's life at risk.
</summary>
<year>2014</year>
</meta>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/gomorrah.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjY5MDA2ZjktOWI1My00NzBiLTk1NWEtYjc5YmQzMDNiNmI2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjM2OTA5MjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,706,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc1Njg4MDAyN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTU3NDY1OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1513,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Goliath</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Billy Mcbride is going through a rough patch. He has been fired from the law firm he helped build, his wife has left him, and he is now a down on his luck ambulance chaser. A lady approaches him to represent her in a wrongful death case. After reluctantly accepting to take on the case a series of strange events befall Billy. Through death threats, harassment and trumped up arrests, Billy embarks on obtaining justice, and it is one hell of a ride.
1h | Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/goliath.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI0MzQ4Mzk0Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODE2MzM0NTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzg4N2NiYmYtNDY2ZS00NTU3LWIyZmEtZWZmZjk5NjNhYjI0L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDAxOTExNTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Gotham</title>
  <summary>Storyline
In crime ridden Gotham City, Thomas and Martha Wayne are murdered before young Bruce Wayne's eyes. Although the idealistic Gotham City Police Dept. detective James Gordon, and his cynical partner, Harvey Bullock, seem to solve the case quickly, things are not so simple. Inspired by Bruce's traumatized desire for justice, Gordon vows to find it amid Gotham's corruption. Thus begins Gordon's lonely quest that would set him against his own comrades and the underworld with their own deadly rivalries and mysteries. In the coming wars, innocence will be lost and compromises will be made as some criminals will fall as casualties while others will rise as supervillains. All the while, young Bruce observes this war with a growing obsession that would one day drive him to seek his own justice against the evil of Gotham as The Batman.
15 | 42min | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2014– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/gotham.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjI5MjAwNTg0NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDk1NTk4OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,665,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjAwNzY5NDg1OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjg2Mzk1NjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Grey's Anatomy</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A medical based drama centered around Meredith Grey, an aspiring surgeon and daughter of one of the best surgeons, Dr. Ellis Grey. Throughout the series, Meredith goes through professional and personal challenges along with fellow surgeons at Seattle Grace Hospital.
15 | 41min | Drama, Romance | TV Series (2005– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/greysanatomy.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTY5OTNjNTctMWYxNC00YjE2LWEzMTMtMTIzMzQ1MzhkODRhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzAzNTY3MDM@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjQ1OTgwODMxNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTg4OTkxMg@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Hannibal</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Explores the early relationship between the renowned psychiatrist and his patient, a young FBI criminal profiler, who is haunted by his ability to empathize with serial killers.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/hannibal.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMGRhMzFjYjMtYzZiZS00OTI0LWIzN2MtMDU0MGY5MTBkZjE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzkwMjQ5NzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,679,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE5MjgyODMxOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTEwODY1NjM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Hawaii Five-0</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Steve McGarrett comes to Hawaii to avenge his father's death but when the governor offers his own task force, he accepts. He picks up team members on the way, Danny Williams, the head detective on his father's case, Chin Ho Kelly, a former HPD Detective who was fired for accused corruption and McGarrett's father's old patrol partner, Kono Kalakaua, a Cadet at the Police Academy who's 1 week from graduating, Lori Weston entry to Five-O temporarily, how Catharine Rollins a girl friend of Steve and Captain Lou Grover, a former Chicago PD Head of SWAT.
42min | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2010– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/hawaii50.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BM2Q2OTQyN2MtYWY1ZC00NzY0LWEzZDgtYmQyZWNlODE0NTAyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzAyOTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ2NDMzODU1NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTQzNTk4Mw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>House M.D. </title>
<summary>Storyline
An antisocial maverick doctor who specializes in diagnostic medicine does whatever it takes to solve puzzling cases that come his way using his crack team of doctors and his wits.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/drhouse.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDA4NjQzN2ItZDhhNC00ZjVlLWFjNTgtMTEyNDQyOGNjMDE1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,679,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA0NjUwNjc5Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjMxMjY5MDI@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>House Of Cards</title>
<summary>Storyline
A Congressman works with his equally conniving wife to exact revenge on the people who betrayed him.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/houseofcards.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODM1MDU2NjY5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDkxNTcwNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxMjg2Mzc3Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzAzNDgxMjI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,721_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Humans</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Humans is set in a parallel present where the latest must-have gadget for any busy family is a Synth - a highly-developed robotic servant eerily similar to its live counterpart. In the hope of transforming the way they live, one strained suburban family purchases a refurbished synth only to discover that sharing life with a machine has far-reaching and chilling consequences.
12 | 42min | Drama, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/humans.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ3NjE2OTY4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTE0NDc0ODE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE1NzcyNzI4N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzA3OTQxNTM@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>How I Met Your Mother</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  A father recounts to his children, through a series of flashbacks, the journey he and his four best friends took leading up to him meeting their mother.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/howimetyourmother.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWJjMDEzZjUtYWE1Yy00M2ZiLThlMmItODljNTAzODFiMzc2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzA1ODExODM4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDgyMDc3ODE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Impractical Jokers </title>
  <summary>Storyline
Each episode contains a regime of multiple challenges in teams, independently or against specific jokers in a head to head challenge. Every time they fail to complete a task the joker will receive a red thumbs down. The joker with the most thumbs down after the series of challenges is the loser who has to complete an extremely embarrassing or difficult task in which the jokers cannot say no to. These Loser Challenges have consisted of dangerous stunts and some scary scenes!
15 | 30min | Comedy, Reality-TV | TV Series (2011– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/impracticaljokers.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg4ODkwODAzMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDMwNDM5NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,701,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIyOTc2ODk0NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODAyNjA2Nw@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1461,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Insecure</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Follows the awkward experiences and racy tribulations of a modern-day African-American woman.
15 | 30min | Comedy | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/insecure.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk5NTA2MDEyNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDUwMDE3MjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMwMTY5ODg5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDQ1Mzk5OTE@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Instinct</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Former CIA operative is lured back to his old life when the NYPD needs his help to stop a serial killer. Dr. Dylan Reinhart (Alan Cumming) is a gifted author and university professor living a quiet life teaching psychopathic behavior to packed classes of adoring students. But when top NYPD detective Lizzie Needham (Bojana Novakovic) appeals to him to help her catch a serial murderer who is using Dylan's first book as a tutorial, Dylan is compelled by the case, comes out of retirement and taps into his old skill set. Though Dylan and Lizzie initially clash, when it comes to catching killers, they realize they will make an ideal team if they both trust their instincts. Based on the James Patterson book.
1h | Crime, Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/instinct.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTE5Njc0OWQtZDE5ZS00YzhiLWI4MWMtNGMzMDViNTc1MzkyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzE5MTM1NTQ@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,731,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZWIyM2JkMjktN2I5Yi00ZDg4LThhYTktNjJkYjU4ODliZmMzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzE5MTM1NTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Into The Badlands</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Regent Sunny, a highly-skilled fighter and the deadliest "Head Clipper" for Baron Quinn battles the Nomads to rescue a mysterious boy named M.K. who harbors a dark secret about his past. But when he brings him back to The Fort to train as a "Colt", a Clipper-in-training, things quickly get out of hand with another trainee. When first blood is drawn, M.K. loses control of himself as if something takes over his body, making the boy valuable to an opposing baron, The Widow. Meanwhile, Sunny discovers M.K.'s pendant has the same image as the one on his childhood compass of a place called Azra, the boy's home. In order to seek out the truth about his own past, Sunny wants to know more of this city beyond the Badlands, and must find a way out, especially now that his lover Veil is illegally pregnant with his child.
15 | 42min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/intothebadlands.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzkyOTcwMTAwMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTk3NzIzMTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE2NDcxMTIyNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDY2NTEzNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Iron Fist </title>
  <summary>Storyline
Danny Rand returns to New York City after being missing for years, trying to reconnect with his past and his family legacy. He fights against the criminal element corrupting his world around him with his incredible kung-fu mastery and ability to summon the awesome power of the fiery Iron Fist
18 | 55min | Action, Adventure, Crime | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/ironfist.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI5Mjg1NDcyOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjAxOTQ5MTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY1Mjg2NzcxMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzUyNDczMTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia </title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Five friends with big egos and slightly arrogant attitudes are the proprietors of an Irish bar in Philadelphia.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/sunnyphiladelphia.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjI2NDIwNjk0OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTczNjE5NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDEyMTRmNjctMWY1Ny00MjhmLWIzMjQtOWRhYzhhNmMyZGUwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjIyMTc0ODQ@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>iZombie</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Liv Moore, a medical student, gets invited in a party which turns into a macabre zombie arena. Liv wakes up from the dead and becomes a zombie. For maintaining her humanity she must eat human brains so she began working in coroner's office to access brains. Eating a brain gives her memories and traits of that person. So she helps detective Clive Babineaux to solve the murder as a psychic.
12 | 42min | Comedy, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/izombie.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzM1NjE5Mjg4MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDU3MzU4NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,662,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDg3OTI3NGMtMDhiMC00NGZiLTlkM2ItMGRhNGUxNThlYWI0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzU4NDAwNjA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Justified</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Old-school U.S. Marshal Raylan Givens is reassigned from Miami to his childhood home in the poor, rural coal mining towns in eastern Kentucky.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/justified.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM0MDYzODA1MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDE5MTkxNDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2QyZjExN2YtNmZiNC00MDg4LTg4ZDctMDQ2MzBkZGE0ZTNjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjEwNDMwNzI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Kevin Can Wait</title>
  <summary>Storyline
KEVIN CAN WAIT stars Kevin James as a retired police officer who is setting out on a fresh career path as he rises to the challenge of being a newly single dad. His kids, Sara, Jack and Kendra, are grateful to him for making sure they're OK but decide it's time for him to get out of the house, so they turn to Vanessa (Leah Remini), his former police partner, for help. Vanessa has left the force to launch her own private security firm, and she makes Kevin an offer he can't refuse - to be her new business partner. Although the job isn't always glamorous and they rarely see eye to eye, Kevin and Vanessa share an undeniable bond from their years working together. Also, Kendra and her fiancé, Chale, face issues of their own, including becoming newlyweds and figuring out how they will support themselves. Once again, life has thrown Kevin some curveballs, so his dreams of an early retirement will just have to wait a little longer, and his family will always come first.
30min | Comedy | TV Series (2016–2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/kevincanwait.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTM3MGUwNTItNmIyYi00NjFiLTg5NWQtYzRlYzY3ODY3YTM1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzAyOTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDU5OTQ3NTI2NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjU4NTc0OTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Kidding</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Jeff, aka Mr. Pickles, is an icon of children's television, a beacon of kindness and wisdom to America's impressionable young minds and the parents who grew up with him - who also anchors a multimillion-dollar branding empire. But when this beloved personality's family - wife, two sons, sister and father - begins to implode, Jeff finds no fairy tale or fable or puppet will guide him through the crisis, which advances faster than his means to cope. The result: a kind man in a cruel world faces a slow leak of sanity as hilarious as it is heartbreaking.
22min | Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/kidding.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZmU5YmIzMWQtNTRmYS00NWFmLWFkODctYTAzYjQ5ODM1ODllXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWI1ZjVkN2EtNDFiZS00YjQ0LWE1M2QtMGY0YWFhNWUyMjIzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjUwNzk3NDc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Killjoys</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Killjoys is a fast paced space adventure about a trio of hard-living, party-loving bounty hunters working for the R.A.C (Recovery and Apprehension Coalition). An Independent interplanetary organization of assassins and retrieval experts, who are known across the J cluster as Killjoys. The show centers on their lives and activities in the Quad, a heavily populated solar system, ruled by a tyrannical class based corporation known as the company. With the whole system verging on revolutionary war and their own bloody pasts finally catching up with them. The three struggle daily to maintain their R.A.C neutrality by focusing on the only law a Killjoy won't break "The Warrant is all".
15 | 42min | Action, Adventure, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/killjoys.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzk3NzEyMzYwNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDIzNTAyOTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjAxMjk0ODQ3NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDM2NjEwNjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Krypton</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Set two generations before the destruction of the legendary Man of Steel's home planet, KRYPTON follows Superman's grandfather - whose House of El was ostracized and shamed - as he fights to redeem his family's honor and save his beloved world from chaos.
45min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/krypton.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTkxNDM1NzkyNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjg2MzU4NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,668,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ5OTY4N2UtNzIwMC00MjNhLTlhZDgtOTliMmQ2MGI3YzU2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzEyNjkxNzQ@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<name>La casa de papel</name>
<summary>Storyline
A group of very peculiar robbers assault the Factory of Moneda and Timbre to carry out the most perfect robbery in the history of Spain and take home 2.4 billion euros.
</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/lacasadepapel.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzBlY2QzNzYtMWU1NS00NjFkLWJiMzItYmM3YTc4MDFjNDQwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTA0MjU0Ng@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,667,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzczM2YwNTYtN2E2ZS00ZDYyLWJkMTAtMTBhNGVkM2ExZTkwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzE5ODM5NTY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Last Man Standing</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Mike Baxter is the marketing director for an iconic outdoor sporting goods store. He loves to have adventures while he's traveling for work and, of course, he drives a pick-up truck. While Mike is king of the hill at work, he's the odd man out in a home that is dominated by women -- namely his wife, Vanessa, and their three daughters, 20- year-old Kristin, 17-year-old Mandy and 13-year-old Eve. After being a stay-at-home mom for years, Vanessa recently returned to the workplace and was quickly promoted (much to the dismay of her primarily male co-workers). As a result of Vanessa's increased work load, Mike is pulled into more hands-on parenting than ever before.
30min | Comedy | TV Series (2011– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/lastmanstanding.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA1MTQxMzU4NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTcwNDIxNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjRiZTBkNzktMGMwYi00OWYyLTg5ODQtN2ZmOGRiZDFhYjkxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Legends of Tomorrow</title>
  <summary>Storyline
When heroes alone are not enough... the world needs legends. Having seen the future, Rip Hunter will desperately try to prevent certain events from happening, by time-traveling; Now Rip Hunter is tasked with assembling a desperate group of heroes and villains to confront an unstoppable threat - not only is the planet at stake, but our timeline itself. The Great Question being asked here is can this ragtag team defeat an immortal threat unlike anything they have ever known?
12 | 42min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/legendsoftomorrow.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODVjYzliMTQtODk0My00MmUxLTkwMzMtMWJjMGQzZmU5MzAwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc4MjczMTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BY2YxZWEyMjUtZjQ0NS00M2UzLWJlMDAtYTM4ZGMyNDYxOTBkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTc4MjczMTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Legion</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Legion, based on the Marvel Comics by Chris Claremont and Bill Sienkiewicz, is the story of David Haller (Dan Stevens), a troubled young man who may be more than human. Diagnosed as schizophrenic as a child, David has been in and out of psychiatric hospitals for years. Now in his early 20's and free once again, David loses himself in the rhythm of the structured regimen of daily life: breakfast, lunch, dinner, therapy, medications, sleep. David spends the rest of his time in companionable silence alongside his chatterbox friend Lenny (Aubrey Plaza), a fellow patient whose life-long drug and alcohol addiction has done nothing to quell her boundless optimism that her luck is about to change. The pleasant numbness of David's routine is completely upended with the arrival of a beautiful and troubled new patient named Syd (Rachel Keller). Inexplicably drawn to one another, David and Syd share a startling encounter, after which David must confront the shocking possibility that the voices he hears and the visions he sees may actually be real.
  15 | 1h | Action, Drama, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/legion.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjQyOTQ3Njc5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzgyNjAxNTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYTQxYTIxNjAtNDliMi00MmUwLWJlMGQtMjFlOWM2MTliM2NhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjAwNTYwNDg@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Lethal Weapon</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A slightly unhinged cop is partnered with a veteran detective trying to maintain a low stress level in his life.
15 | 44min | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/lethalweapon.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA3MjU2MTc5MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDk3Mjc3OTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYTQwYjhkMjEtZmQzNS00ZGVjLWJlOWEtMzA2NDNmY2I4ODljXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc5Mjg0NjU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1444,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Life Sentence</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Stella (Lucy Hale) has lived the last 8 years of her life making everyday count. 8 years ago she was diagnosed with cancer, but when she finds out that her cancer has been cured, she struggles to make some life choices. How do you make choices when there isn't a weight on your shoulders anymore?
44min | Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/lifesentence.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjIyMTE5MjMyMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjc3MTA4NDM@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMWM3YTgyNDQtNjYyMC00YWMxLTllOGQtM2E5YTYyNDJiMTk0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Lodge 49</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Doug finds himself deposited by fate at the doorstep of Lodge 49, a dusty fraternal order that offers cheap beer and strange alchemical philosophies.
Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/lodge49.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY2YmRlZmEtN2EwMC00MzE4LWIyOTctNWViMzg2NTQ0OWVhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTg5NTI4MjE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY2YmRlZmEtN2EwMC00MzE4LWIyOTctNWViMzg2NTQ0OWVhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTg5NTI4MjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Lost In Space</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Set 30 years in the future, colonization in space is now a reality, and the Robinson family is among those tested and selected to make a new life for themselves in a better world. But when the new colonists find themselves abruptly torn off course en route to their new home they must forge new alliances and work together to survive in a dangerous alien environment, light-years from their original destination. Stranded along with the Robinsons are two outsiders who find themselves thrown together by circumstance and a mutual knack for deception. The charismatic Dr. Smith is a master manipulator with an inscrutable end game. And the roguish, but charming Don West is a highly-skilled, blue collar contractor, who had no intention of joining the colony, let alone crash landing on a lost planet.
12 | 1h | Adventure, Drama, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/lostinspace.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjI3MjI5OTczNV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODA4MTc5NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMDIwZmUxZmEtZDc4ZC00ZGM4LTkyMTQtY2M2MDM2ZjVkZmE4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODExNTExMTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Lost</title>
<imdb>tt0411008</imdb>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/lost.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzhlY2E5NDUtYjJjYy00ODg3LWFkZWQtYTVmMzU4ZWZmOWJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,647,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc2OTAxOTU4NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDU3MzE0MzI@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Lucifer</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Lucifer, bored from his sulking life in hell, comes to live in Los Angeles. While there, he helps humanity with its miseries through his experience and telepathic abilities to bring people's deepest desires and thoughts out of them. While meeting with a girl in his nightclub (called Lux), a shootout involving him and the girl leads him to become a LAPD consultant who tries to punish people for their crimes through law and justice.
15 | 42min | Crime, Drama, Fantasy | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/lucifer.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOGQxNWY5NDUtN2VkOS00N2RiLThhMWQtNmExYmJhMzE3NDAwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzE3NDUwODA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZjkxODg2MzUtY2YxNy00MTA3LTkwMzktMzA3MWU5MGY4OTEyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTgzOTI2MA@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Luke Cage</title>
<summary>Storyline
After a sabotaged experiment leaves him with super strength and unbreakable skin, Luke Cage becomes a fugitive trying to rebuild his life in modern day Harlem, New York City. But he is soon pulled out of the shadows and must fight a battle for the heart of his city - forcing him to confront a past he had tried to bury.
15 | 55min | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/lukecage.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTcyMzc1MjI5MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzE4ODY2OTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,704,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOGEwOWI4ZTktN2ZhMC00OGQ2LThiNDAtOGEzYzVmNTc2MDQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjg2MTMyNTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>MacGyver</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A reimagining of the classic series, is an action-adventure drama about 20-something Angus "Mac" MacGyver, who creates the Department of External Services (DXS), a clandestine organization within the U.S. government where he uses his extraordinary talent for unconventional problem-solving and vast scientific knowledge to save lives. Joining his team on high-risk missions around the globe is maverick former CIA agent Jack Dalton; Patricia Thornton, an ex-field agent turned director of operations; and Riley Davis, an unpredictable computer hacker with a chip on her shoulder. At home, MacGyver is entertained by his ambitious roommate, Wilt Bozer. Under the aegis of the Department of External Services, MacGyver takes on the responsibility of saving the world, armed to the teeth with resourcefulness and little more than bubble gum and a paper clip.
12 | 43min | Action , Adventure , Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/macgyver.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDliYzI2YTUtN2ZmZC00M2QwLWJkYzQtZGQ0ZmZlMGJmYjJmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzAyOTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY3NjU2NDQ5Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjkxMjc1MDI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mad Men </title>
  <summary>Storyline
  A drama about one of New York's most prestigious ad agencies at the beginning of the 1960s, focusing on one of the firm's most mysterious but extremely talented ad executives, Donald Draper.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/madmen.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMwNzk5Nzg2OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjg1OTk1NDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,685,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjYwYmFkNGItMTFhYi00ZjI5LTlkY2YtMGM0YzRhMDUzMWIyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjM0ODg2Njk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Magnum P.I.</title>
  <summary>Storyline
An ex-Navy SEAL returns home from Afghanistan and uses his military skills to become a private investigator in Hawaii.
43min | Action , Adventure , Crime | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/magnumpi.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzBhOGVhNmUtNGIwNy00YmQ5LWEzMDQtNWI5Njc5YmUyMzAxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,659,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3MDY3MzUwM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjg0ODYwNjM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Making a Murderer</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Filmed over a 10-year period, Steven Avery, a DNA exoneree who, while in the midst of exposing corruption in local law enforcement, finds himself the prime suspect in a grisly new crime.
15 | 1h | Documentary, Crime | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/makingamurderer.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg4Mjc1NjE4Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjk2NjA1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg4Mjc1NjE4Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjk2NjA1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Manifest</title>
  <summary>Storyline
After a turbulent, but routine, flight the passengers and crew discover the world has aged five years, yet no time has passed for them, and soon a deeper mystery unfolds.
43min | Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/manifest.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMmY4NjRmZDMtYmZjOS00OWI2LTlmMjktYjg3N2FiNzg4OTA1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWEyZGM0NmQtYzNlNy00NzhmLWI1NmQtODNjNjBjOTRkMjE5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Man With A Plan</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A dad finds out that parenting is harder than he thought after his wife goes back to work and he's left at home to take care of the kids.
30min | Comedy | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/manwithaplan.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjYwMzJiOGEtMjk4Ni00NDI0LTkxMDMtNTI3M2ZmZjFhZTgwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzAyOTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ5OTYwNjg5N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDM5NDUwMDI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Marlon</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A loving (but immature) father with a larger-than-life personality is committed to co-parenting his two kids with his very-together ex-wife but for Marlon family really always does come first - even if he's the biggest kid of all.
22min | Comedy | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/marlon.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODI2NWVkYWQtNzVjNS00YjM2LWE0MGQtNTk5ZWI2OTI1ZTk0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjEyNjg2NDE0MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODY5ODE5ODE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mayans M.C.</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Set in a post-Jax Teller world, "Mayans MC" sees EZ Reyes, a former golden boy now fresh out of prison, as a prospect in the Mayan MC charter on the California-Mexico border who must carve out his new outlaw identity.
1h | Crime, Drama, Thriller | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/mayans.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTY5MzBiNmEtOGE0MS00YzYzLWE3MGYtNmYwMDdiNzZiMDU5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTMxODk2OTU@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjljODRmZDUtYmJjYi00NjVhLWJlMGUtZjZmYmRlN2E0MjNiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjgwMzc5Nzk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1086,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Midnight, Texas</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Follows the lives of the inhabitants of a small town where the concept of normal is relative. A haven for vampires, witches, psychics, hit men, and others with extraordinary backgrounds, Midnight gives outsiders a place to belong. The town members form a strong and unlikely family as they work together to fend off the pressures of unruly biker gangs, questionable police officers, and shades of their own dangerous pasts.
1h | Drama , Fantasy , Mystery | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/midnighttexas.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2QzYWZmZjAtNzFkOS00NzgwLWIzZDgtNmRkMTM5N2RkMmEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODUxOTU0OTg@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMyMjk1OTQ3Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTY5ODE5ODE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Modern Family</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Told from the perspective of an unseen documentary filmmaker, the series offers an honest, often-hilarious perspective of family life. Parents Phil and Claire yearn for an honest, open relationship with their three kids. But a daughter who is trying to grow up too fast, another who is too smart for her own good, and a rambunctious young son make it challenging. Claire's dad, Jay, and his Latina wife, Gloria, are raising two sons together, but people sometimes believe Jay to be Gloria's father. Jay's gay son, Mitchell, and his partner, Cameron, have adopted a little Asian girl, completing one big -- straight, gay, multicultural, traditional happy family.
12 | 22min | Comedy, Romance | TV Series (2009– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/modernfanily.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTI5MjUyYjUtMzhmOC00NTc3LWIzMTctMTVlOTA2NjI2NDU2XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzAzNTY3MDM@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjQwMzcwNjgwMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjQwNDc4OTE@._V1_SY1000_SX750_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mom</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Single mom Christy has her hands full with two children, Violet and Roscoe, and maintaining newfound sobriety, when her passive-aggressive, recovering-alcoholic mother re-enters the picture, brimming with criticisms about Christy's life. As the daughter works to be the best mother she can and to overcome mistakes she made, she must also navigate dysfunctional relationships with romantic interests, and with her irresponsible ex-husband, Baxter. Despite the uphill battle, Christy tries to remain positive and stay on a path to help her reach her goals.
30min | Comedy, Drama, Romance | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/mom.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNWI0ZjU4MzUtMTdmMy00OWVkLThhNWItNzQ4NDEyNTBiY2ZjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzAyOTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODg3MTQwNjg3M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDIwNDg5MTE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Murdoch Mysteries</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  In the 1890s, William Murdoch uses radical forensic techniques for the time, including fingerprinting and trace evidence, to solve some of the city's most gruesome murders.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/murdochmysteries.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMwNjkzNDU4Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMDUxMTAyOA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODI5ODQzMzc2NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMTUxMTAyOA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1505,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mr. Mercedes</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Tells the story of a psychopathic killer who drives a stolen Mercedes into a crowd and a recently retired detective who tries to bring him down.
1h | Thriller | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/mrmercedes.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA0MTU2NzgyNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDYwMzY3NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmM2ZWI4MjYtZDY0NS00NjU3LWEwYzktMmMzZjJmNDU2MDViXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzQ5MjI0ODI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Mr. Robot</title>
  <summary>Summary
  Elliot is a brilliant introverted young programmer who works as a cyber-security engineer by day and vigilante hacker by night. He also happens to be suffering from a strange condition similar to schizophrenia which he futilely tries to keep under control by regularly taking both legal and illegal drugs and visiting his therapist. When a strange feisty young woman named Darlene and a secretive middle-aged man calling himself Mr. Robot, who claims to be the mysterious leader of an underground hacking group known as F-Society, offer Elliot a chance to take his vigilantism to the next level and help them take down E-Corp, the corrupt multi-national financial company that Elliot works for and likes to call Evil Corp, Elliot finds himself at the crossroads. Mr. Robot, who has personal reasons for wanting to take down E-Corp, also reveals that he already has one ally, an even more mysterious, secretive and highly dangerous shadowy hacking group known only as Dark Army. Meanwhile, Elliot's childhood and only friend, Angela, who blames E-Corp for the death of their parents, tries to take down E-Corp legally by joining their ranks and trying to dig up evidence of their corruption from the inside. A wild card in this scheme becomes Tyrell Wellick, an unhinged psychopathic E-Corp yuppie, originally from Scandinavia, who has a very unusual relationship with his dominant and ambitious wife Joanna. After many twists and turns, Mr. Robot's plan is finally put in motion - with catastrophic (un)intended results. But that's just the end of the beginning of the real story.
  18 | 49min | Crime , Drama , Thriller | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/mrrobot.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYzMDE2MzI4MF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTkxODgxOTE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDRlY2EzYjUtMzRhMi00NmRhLTgxZTMtZDAwZWYzZTlkYWM3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODg3NDc0NTg@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Narcos</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Narcos tells the true-life story of the growth and spread of cocaine drug cartels across the globe and attendant efforts of law enforcement to meet them head on in brutal, bloody conflict. It centers around the notorious Colombian cocaine kingpin Pablo Escobar (Wagner Moura) and Steve Murphy (Holbrook), a DEA agent sent to Colombia on a U.S. mission to capture him and ultimately kill him.
15 | 49min | Biography , Crime , Drama | TV Series (2015–2017)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/narcos.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmU5ZGQyZDUtMmU3OC00ZTZkLTk4YzItYzg5NDNkMmJlZjMwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjU2ODM5MjU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGVhODUzOGMtYzE0Ny00YTc5LTliMTMtMWUxYmRjYzI0YjVkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3NjU4MzA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Narcos: Mexico </title>
  <summary>Storyline
Narcos: Mexico exploring the origins of the modern drug war by going back to its roots, beginning at a time when the Mexican trafficking world was a loose and disorganized confederation of independent growers and dealers. Witness the rise of the Guadalajara Cartel in the 1980s as Félix Gallardo takes the helm, unifying traffickers in order to build an empire. When DEA agent Kiki Camarena moves his wife and young son from California to Guadalajara to take on a new post, he quickly learns that his assignment will be more challenging than he ever could have imagined. As Kiki garners intelligence on Félix and becomes more entangled in his mission, a tragic chain of events unfold, affecting the drug trade and the war against it for years to come.
18 | 50min | Crime , Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/narcosmexico.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTcyODAxNzcwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzM1Mjc1NjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjNiMmJhZTEtNTIxZi00MDE1LWJlNmMtMzFjYmMzY2U1ZWJhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzUyNjY1NDU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>New Amsterdam</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Dr. Max Goodwin is brilliant, charming -- and the new medical director at America's oldest public hospital. While he's set on tearing down the bureaucracy to provide exceptional care, the doctors and staff are not so sure. They've heard this before, and no one else has delivered on those promises. Not taking "no" for an answer, Max disrupts the status quo and proves he will stop at nothing to breathe new life into this understaffed, underfunded and underappreciated hospital -- the only one in the world capable of treating Ebola patients, prisoners from Rikers Island and the president of the United States all under one roof -- and return it to the glory that put it on the map. Inspired by Bellevue in New York City.
43min | Drama | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/newansterdam.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTA2ZGY4NWYtYmNlMy00MDA4LTgyMWYtNzQ5M2JkNGYxNzY1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjQ0ZGE2ZjgtOWM3OC00MGMyLTkyNjAtYTY5MWFiMWNhZWQ5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTExNDQ2MTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Nikita</title>
  <summary>Storyline
When she was a deeply troubled teenager, Nikita was rescued from death row by a secret U.S. agency known only as Division, who faked her execution and told her she was being given a second chance to start a new life and serve her country. What they didn't tell her was that she was being trained as a spy and assassin. Throughout her grueling training at Division, Nikita never lost her humanity, even falling in love with a civilian. When her fiancé was murdered, Nikita realized she had been betrayed and her dreams shattered by the only people she thought she could trust, so she did what no one else before her had been able to do: she escaped. Now, after three years in hiding, Nikita is seeking retribution and making it clear to her former bosses that she will stop at nothing to expose and destroy their covert operation.
1h | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2010–2013)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/nikita.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIxMDAyOTMzMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjE5NTc4NA@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk5MjkzNDQyMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODIwNTM0MjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Orange Is the New Black</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Convicted of a decade old crime of transporting drug money to an ex-girlfriend, normally law abiding Piper Chapman is sentenced to a year and a half behind bars to face the reality of how life changing prison can really be.
15 | 59min | Comedy, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/orangeisthenewblack.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA3MTE5ODM3M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTIyMjQ5NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzRkYjE3MGQtMTJmZi00OTBjLWFjNGYtZTEyMTIyNTFhZTRhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzM4MzUzMjE@._V1_SY1000_SX1600_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Our Cartoon President</title>
  <summary>Storyline
This fresh, cutting-edge comedy presents the truish adventures of Trump's confidants and bon vivants - family, top associates, heads of government, golf pros and anyone else straying into his orbit - intrepidly exploring their histories and their psyches, revealing insights into what makes them so definitively Trumpian. It's a workplace comedy where the office happens to be oval; it's a character study in search of character, as seen through the eyes of an imaginary documentary crew.
30min | Animation, Comedy | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/ourcartoonpresident.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTc4YTdiZmUtOTA0OC00ZDY1LTgzM2EtODFkODM5MTUwZmYzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,653,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDY2Nzk5NjktYTFhOS00MTU4LWJjM2UtZGI3MDIxMGMxMWNmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjM4MTkwNQ@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Once Upon A Time</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  For Emma Swan, life has been anything but a happy ending. But when she's reunited with Henry - the son she gave up for adoption ten years ago - on the night of her 28th birthday, everything changes. The now 10-year-old Henry is in desperate need of Emma's help because he believes from reading a book of fairytales that she's the daughter of Snow White and Prince Charming - who sent her away from the Enchanted Forest to be protected from a curse that was enacted by the Evil Queen. Emma initially refuses to believe a word of Henry's story but soon finds that his hometown of Storybrooke, Maine is more than it seems. Because it's in Storybrooke that all of the classic characters we know are frozen in time with no memories of their former selves - except for the Evil Queen, who is Storybrooke's mayor and Henry's adoptive mother Regina Mills. Now, as the epic "Final Battle" for the future of both worlds approaches, Emma will have to accept her destiny and uncover the mystery behind a place where fairytales are to be believed.
  15 | Adventure, Fantasy, Romance | TV Series (2011–2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/onceuponatime.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjBmZmI0ZDktODI2MS00MDU1LTk0NDYtNGE0MDc0OWVkYzcwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzAzNTY3MDM@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzU1Njc0Y2ItMDRkNi00MWVmLThkMjItYjU4MzA5NTRiODhhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODgzNzA5MA@@._V1_SY1000_SX1500_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>One Dollar</title>
  <summary>Storyline
One Dollar is a mystery set in a small rust belt town in post-recession America, where a one-dollar bill changing hands connects a group of characters involved in a shocking multiple murder. The path of the dollar bill and point of view in each episode paint a picture of a modern American town with deep class and cultural divides that spill out into the open as the town's secrets get revealed.
50min | Drama , Mystery , Thriller | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/onedollar.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODA2MDcxMzAyM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjEzNDQ4NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODA2MDcxMzAyM15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjEzNDQ4NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>One Strange Rock</title>
  <summary>Storyline
The extraordinary story of Earth and why it is special and uniquely brimming with life among a largely unknown but harsh cosmic arena; astronauts tell the story of Earth through unique perspective.
47min | Documentary | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/onestrangerock.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzBlYjhmYTMtNzY1ZS00ZGU2LWFmMzktYTg5ZGU1N2JlMGRmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTg3MDg4NzM@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTk1MWI3ODUtZDAwNC00NDJjLTliNTctYWFjMDUzYTBhZjlhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Ozark</title>
  <summary>Storyline
The Byrdes and their teenage kids, Charlotte and Jonah, are, for all intents and purposes, an ordinary family with ordinary lives. Except for the job of Marty, a Chicago financial advisor who also serves as the top money launderer for the second largest drug cartel in Mexico. When things go awry, Marty must uproot his family from the skyscrapers of Chicago and relocate to the lazy lake region of the Missouri Ozarks.
18 | 1h | Crime, Drama, Thriller | TV Series (2017– )
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/ozark.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjIwOTEwMDk4MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTY1NTEwNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMGQxZjdiOTgtNjkyZC00ODRjLWJhY2EtZjA3YWI1OTQxNjYzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTExNDQ2MTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Parks and Recreation</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  The absurd antics of an Indiana town's public officials as they pursue sundry projects to make their city a better place.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/parksandrecreation.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjA5MjUxNDgwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDI5NjMwNDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDliYWIwYjUtZGFkMi00M2UyLWEzNjktYWE2ODUyZWI1YWNkL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjczODAwNDg@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Peaky Blinders</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A gangster family epic set in 1919 Birmingham, England; centered on a gang who sew razor blades in the peaks of their caps, and their fierce boss Tommy Shelby.
15 | 1h | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/peakyblinders.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkzNjEzMDEzMF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDI0MjE4MjE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk1NDgzMjY3Ml5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTk0MjE0MDE@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Person of Interest </title>
  <summary>Storyline
  An ex-assassin and a wealthy programmer save lives via a surveillance AI that sends them the identities of civilians involved in impending crimes. However, the details of the crimes--including the civilians' roles--are left a mystery.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/personofinterest.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZDU1NzA5YzUtNTdmNy00NTVjLWFhNzEtYWI1NmNkNTA1ZDBhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzlkZTQ5OTgtMDk0ZS00Mjc0LWIwNWEtYmFmNWQ3MWZiMmY0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjg2MTMyNTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1504,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Power</title>
  <summary>Storyline
"Power" tells the story of James "Ghost" St. Patrick, a wealthy New York City nightclub owner who caters to the city's elite. He wants to build an empire, turn the club into a Fortune 500 business, but there's just one problem: Ghost is living a double life. When he is not in the club, he is the kingpin of the most lucrative drug network in New York for a very high-level clientele. His marriage, family and business all become unknowingly threatened as he is tempted to leave his criminal life behind and become the rags-to-riches businessman he wants to be most of all.
50min | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2014– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/power.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTA4NTkzMjUzOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzg5ODkxOTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTkwNDE4MDQxN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTkxODA5NTE@._V1_SY1000_SX1500_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Preacher</title>
  <summary>Storyline
What if an angel and a demon procreate? What would that offspring be? Would it be holy or demonic or both? Preacher Is that tale. The offspring has no body, just a soul. That soul needs a body and chose Jessie. A preacher from Texas with a loss of faith and a drinking problem. The offspring called Genesis bonds with Jesse giving him the word of God. What he says is done.
18 | 1h | Adventure, Drama, Fantasy | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/preacher.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZWE3ZTEwZmYtNjRkNy00M2E2LTlhOWQtNTNjYjZiNTdkMjgzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjEwNTM2Mzc@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg1ODY5MjE5NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjMwNDUyNTM@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Prison Break</title>
<summary>Storyline
Due to a political conspiracy, an innocent man is sent to death row and his only hope is his brother, who makes it his mission to deliberately get himself sent to the same prison in order to break the both of them out, from the inside.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/prisonbreak.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTg3NTkwNzAxOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwMjM1NjI5MQ@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2FkNjVkMjEtMmYzMy00MTllLWI0NTYtM2UwOTc1YWMxM2E0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTgyNDM1OTU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1315,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Quantico</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A look at the lives of young FBI recruits training at the Quantico base in Virginia when one of them is suspected of being a sleeper terrorist.
15 | 42min | Crime, Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2015–2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/quantico.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOGRhZDJmMjMtZmYxNS00MTE0LTlhYmYtY2IyYjBjOGY0MjcxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzAzNTY3MDM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOWQ3YTIxMzUtY2I4ZS00ZGYwLWEyY2ItM2ViYTVmYWJkZDFiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODgzNzA5MA@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Ransom</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Ransom is inspired by the professional experiences of crisis negotiator Laurent Combalbert who with his partner, Marwan Mery, are among the top negotiators in the world. Together, they travel around the globe to help multinational corporations and governmental agencies with complex negotiations and conflict resolution.
44min | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2017–2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/ransom.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOWExMmRhMWItYmUyMi00MjYzLTk5ODQtMTdkZmU3MWZmMjcyL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BN2E0MTM2ZGYtZjVhNC00NzQ4LWI2ZDQtZGE4Yjk5NmIxNGU3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTY2OTA1Mg@@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,547_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Ray Donovan</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Set in the sprawling mecca of the rich and famous, Ray Donovan does the dirty work for LA's top power players as the go-to guy who makes the problems of the city's celebrities, superstar athletes, and business moguls disappear. This powerful drama unfolds when his father is unexpectedly released from prison, setting off a chain of events that shakes the Donovan family to its core.
15 | 1h | Crime , Drama | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/raydonovan.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWMwMjUyYmMtODYyOS00YjYwLWE0NjQtMGJiYzVmOGVjOGQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTA3MTMyOTk@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWJmMWM3YmEtNGJkNi00OTVjLTk3YzEtNzJiZDdjOTM1ZGVjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc5Mjg0NjU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Reverie</title>
  <summary>Storyline
This grounded new thriller follows Mara Kint, a former hostage negotiator and expert on human behavior, who became a college professor after facing an unimaginable personal tragedy. But when she's brought in to save ordinary people who have lost themselves in a highly advanced virtual-reality program in which you can literally live your dreams, she finds that in saving others, she may actually have discovered a way to save herself.
1h | Drama, Thriller | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/reverie.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzczN2QxYjItNGNjMi00YmNiLWIzM2MtMDRkMDNmMGMzMGZlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzczN2QxYjItNGNjMi00YmNiLWIzM2MtMDRkMDNmMGMzMGZlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Riverdale</title>
  <summary>Storyline
After the death of one of the rich and popular Blossom twins on the 4th of July, the small town of Riverdale investigates the murder. The series starts in September, the beginning of a new school year, that brings with it new students, relationships, and reveals the mysteries of the past 4th of July.
12 | 45min | Crime, Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/riverdale.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZDNmNmI5MGItMjUyOC00ODg4LWE0NmEtMzg5MjUzOWI2MDcwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjYzNDE4ODA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYzNiMDgwNTItNzkyNi00MTk1LTgwOGYtZWVmZDI2ZDhmOTJiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTQ0MDQyMTg@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Rick and Morty </title>
<summary>Storyline
An animated series that follows the exploits of a super scientist and his not-so-bright grandson.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/rickandmorty.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjRiNDRhNGUtMzRkZi00MThlLTg0ZDMtNjc5YzFjYmFjMmM4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzQ1ODk3MTQ@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjNmMjU3ZGUtZTdiMi00NDdlLTg0NTUtNDE4NzMwYTczYjAwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzYzMzM2Mzg@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Room 104</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Set in a single room of an average American hotel, telling a different story of the assorted guests who pass through.
30min | Drama, Horror, Thriller | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/room104.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE2ODg0MjU3NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzQwMTg3MjI@._V1_SY1000_SX675_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjEyOTVjY2YtMDVhMy00MjA3LWFmNTktZDRlNDQ1N2U4ODMxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzY0MTE3NzU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1333,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Santa Clarita Diet</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Sheila and Joel are married real estate agents in Santa Clarita, California. When Sheila dies, their lives take a dark turn.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/santaclaritadiet.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYxMjA3ODkxN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDkzNjk5NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZTc4N2ExNGQtYzdiMC00OGJlLWEyOTAtODU4YzU3MzY0NWMxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDc1MTk4NTA@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Salvation</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Salvation centers on an MIT grad student and a tech superstar who bring a low-level Pentagon official a staggering discovery--that an asteroid is just six months away from colliding with Earth. The show centers on the ramifications of the discovery of an asteroid that will impact the Earth in just six months and the attempts to prevent it.
43min | Drama, Sci-Fi, Thriller | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/salvation.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYzdmMzVhNDctY2QxYS00OTQyLWI0N2EtODdmNDA3M2YwMTQ0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDY2NDU1MzA@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWIzYWNiZTktYjY0MC00MzFjLTk1YjgtNGI4OGQ0MDA4YjMxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTExNDQ2MTI@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Sense8</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Sense8 tells the story of eight strangers: Will (Smith), Riley (Middleton), Capheus (Ameen), Sun (Bae), Lito (Silvestre), Kala (Desai), Wolfgang (Riemelt), and Nomi (Clayton). Each individual is from a different culture and part of the world. In the aftermath of a tragic death they all experience through what they perceive as dreams or visions, they suddenly find themselves growing mentally and emotionally connected. While trying to figure how and why this connection happened and what it means, a mysterious man named Jonas tries to help the eight. Meanwhile, another stranger called Whispers attempts to hunt them down, using the same sensate power to gain full access to a sensate's mind (thoughts/sight) after looking into their eyes. Each episode reflects the views of the characters interacting with each other while delving deeper into their backgrounds and what sets them apart and brings them together with the others.
15 | 1h | Drama, Mystery, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2015–2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/sense8.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA4MTEyMzcwMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTIwODczNTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTUxODc1OTQ2OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTk1MDcxMjI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1497,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Shades of Blue</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Detective Harlee Santos (Jennifer Lopez) is a single mother from New York City, New York. She joins the FBI's anti-corruption task force, whilst dealing with her own financial problems by bribing officers in order to afford for her daughter Cristina (Sarah Jeffery).
1h | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/shadesofblue.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjJjMDA4NTItZWY2Mi00ZWRkLWFlZGQtNTU2ZGY1MDY5YTdmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjMyMTk0NzY1M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTUxMjgwNzE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Shadowhunters: The Mortal Instruments</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Clary Fray is a normal teenager living in Brooklyn with her mother. One day, she discovers that she is descended from a line of Shadowhunters; humans born with angelic blood that fight to protect our world from demons. After her mother is kidnapped, Clary must team up with three Shadowhunters: Jace, Alec and Isabelle and her best friend Simon on a quest to find her mother and recover her past.
12 | 42min | Action, Fantasy, Romance | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/shadowhunters.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTgwMzM3NjQzN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjgxMDQ5NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTM4MDcxMTA5Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjU5MjE4MDI@._V1_SY1000_SX750_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Siren</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Siren takes us inside Bristol Cove - a coastal town known for its legend of once being home to mermaids. When the arrival of a mysterious girl proves this folklore all too true, the battle between man and sea takes a very vicious turn as these predatory beings return to reclaim their right to the ocean.
1h | Drama, Fantasy | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/siren.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZjhiNjZkOWQtNGI3YS00YTczLWE4OWMtYzRhYWVhMGQ2NmJhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjYwNDA2MDE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,676,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTA0MzA2NjEzMzJeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDM4NjA3MTUz._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,991_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Silicon Valley</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Follows the struggle of Richard Hendricks, a Silicon Valley engineer trying to build his own company called Pied Piper.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/silikonvalley.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTAxNTEyODE5MTNeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDE3MjM3ODQz._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOTVmYTY5Y2ItODU1MS00NWMxLTlkNDgtYzA4MDYwNWI3MjU0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTY1MDAxMzc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Six</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Navy SEAL Team Six, whose 2014 mission to eliminate a Taliban leader in Afghanistan goes awry when they uncover a U.S. citizen working with the terrorists. Stemming from an idea by Harvey Weinstein, the drama is inspired by real missions, capturing SEALs' complex personal lives and the life-and-death decisions they make, with each season set in a different location, starting with Africa.
1h | Action, Drama, History | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/six.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjUxNzgzMjMwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjQ2NzczNTM@._V1_SY1000_SX666_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYjUxNDJjYzMtMDdhNy00ZGY4LWE3YTEtODVmY2EzYTZmYzlmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjE5Njk1OTc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Sherlock</title>
<summary>Storyline
A modern update finds the famous sleuth and his doctor partner solving crime in 21st century London.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/sherlock.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWY3NTljMjEtYzRiMi00NWM2LTkzNjItZTVmZjE0MTdjMjJhL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTQ4NTc5OTU@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTczMDEwNTIwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTE5MjgxMTE@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Snowfall</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A look at the early days of the crack cocaine epidemic in Los Angeles during the beginning of the 1980s.
44min | Crime, Drama | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/snowfall.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2Q1NDhhMGUtMjVkNC00OTY3LTkzZWEtOTMwMDkxYjZjYjg3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzA5Mzc0MDc@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDBkMTVhMzItNzFkNi00MGEzLTg2NzAtZGU5YjU0MTY2ZDM3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTM3MDMyMDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Spartacus</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  The inspiration behind this series is the Thracian Gladiator Spartacus, who led a slave uprising against the Roman Republic. The Thracians had been persuaded by Claudius Glaber to serve as auxiliaries in the Roman legions in a campaign against the Getae, who had often plundered Thracian lands. However after Glaber reneges on the deal and switches his attentions from the Getae to attack Mithridates in Asia Minor, the Thracians feel betrayed and mutiny. Captured by Glaber, Spartacus is condemned to death as a Gladiator, whilst his wife Sura is condemned to slavery. Spartacus, however, proves to be a formidable gladiator, and defeats the four gladiators tasked with executing him. He becomes a favorite of the crowd, leading Senator Albinius to commute his death sentence to a life of slavery. Spartacus is purchased by Batiatus for gladiator training, who promises to help him find Sura if he proves himself in training. As the series develops, the story follows the betrayals and machinations of Roman life and a tale of one man's heroic quest for vengeance.
  18 | 55min | Action, Adventure, Biography | TV Series (2010–2013)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/spartacus.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUzOTk3NDQzMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwODY3NzE2Mw@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOWMxYzE0MGUtNjE4OS00MTVhLWI4Y2MtMzRlM2Y2YjIyMGEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzQyOTcyNDY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Sopranos</title>
<summary>Storyline
New Jersey mob boss Tony Soprano deals with personal and professional issues in his home and business life that affect his mental state, leading him to seek professional psychiatric counseling.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/sopranos.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGJjYzhjYTYtMDBjYy00OWU1LTg5OTYtNmYwOTZmZjE3ZDdhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,702,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWFiODI3NWQtNjFiOS00MzEyLThhYTEtOGRmNGNiYTNkN2RiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDEyNjEzOTg@._V1_SY1000_SX1495_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Skam</title>
<summary>Storyline
The story of young teenagers and pupils on Hartvig Nissens upper secondary school in Oslo, and their troubles, scandals and everyday life. Each season is told from a different person's point of view.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/skam.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjY5OGI0NmMtZTI2Zi00MmZjLTk5ZjYtZDk0YjM0YjFiZThiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzk4ODI0MzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,680,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZjgzMjY2MDgtZmU1OC00Y2Y0LThmMWEtODZkNTY1ZTllNTRmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjUzMDMzNzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Star Trek: The Next Generation</title>
<summary>Storyline
Set almost 100 years after Captain Kirk's five-year mission, a new generation of Starfleet officers set off in the U.S.S. Enterprise-D on their own mission to go where no one has gone before.
</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/startrektng.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDViYjAyZWUtNGQxMy00MDUyLTlkZTAtOWNkY2M5ZTk5MTE5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,701,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTUwNzYwMjk5NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzkzODA1NTE@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>


<dir>
  <title>Stan Lee's Lucky Man</title>
  <summary>Storyline
What if you could control luck? Would that be the greatest power you could give a man, or his worst nightmare? From the mind of Stan Lee, the comic book legend, comes a different kind of superhero in this bold crime thriller series about a brilliant but flawed cop who can control luck.
1h | Action, Crime, Drama | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/stanleesluckyman.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjk4MzU5OWEtZmJhMy00NjlmLWExOTktZTcxMzA5NzUyMTM3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjg2MTMyNTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMzg0Njg5NzgwNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTEwODY2NzE@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1267,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Suits</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  While running from a drug deal gone bad, Mike Ross, a brilliant young college dropout, slips into a job interview with one of New York City's best legal closers, Harvey Specter. Tired of cookie-cutter law school grads, Harvey takes a gamble by hiring Mike on the spot after he recognizes his raw talent and photographic memory. Mike and Harvey are a winning team. Even though Mike is a genius, he still has a lot to learn about law. And while Harvey may seem like an emotionless, cold-blooded shark, Mike's sympathy and concern for their cases and clients will help remind Harvey why he went into law in the first place. Mike's other allies in the office include the firm's best paralegal Rachel and Harvey's no-nonsense assistant Donna to help him serve justice. Proving to be an irrepressible duo and invaluable to the practice, Mike and Harvey must keep their secret from everyone including managing partner Jessica and Harvey's arch nemesis Louis, who seems intent on making Mike's life as difficult as possible.
  15 | 44min | Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2011– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/suits.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk1MjYzOTU2Nl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzAxMTg5MTE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE2MTY0MTQ3OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNjkyNjg2NQ@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Supergirl</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Years ago, Krypton was about to explode and Kal-El was sent to Earth to escape that fate. However, his older cousin, Kara, was also intended to accompany the infant as his protector. Unfortunately, Kara was accidentally diverted into the timeless Phantom Zone for years before finally arriving on Earth decades later and found by her cousin who had grown into Superman. Years later, Kara Danvers is a young professional adrift in a thankless job until a fateful crisis ignites a sense of purpose using Kryptonian powers she had long hidden. Inspired, Kara decides to emulate her cousin's superheroic ways, only to find her foster sister introducing her to the secret Department of Extra-Normal Operations, dedicated to fighting alien menaces including those Kara inadvertently led to Earth. Now with such help, the Maid of Might takes her place as Earth's newest champion with new friends and enemies challenging her world.
12 | 43min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/supergirl.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE0MzgxNjYzOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzk3NDUyNTM@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYmVmOTQ2MWEtN2JkYy00MzFkLWI2MDgtMzY4YTgwOGU2NmMxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjcwOTIyMjE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Supernatural</title>
<summary>Storyline
This television drama is about the two Winchester brothers, Sam and Dean, who were raised by their father, John, to hunt and kill all things that go "bump in the night" after his wife, Mary, was murdered by an evil supernatural being when the boys were young. 22 years later the brothers set out on a journey, fighting evil along the way, to find their recently missing father who, when they finally meet up with, reveals he knows what killed their mother, a demon, and has found a way to track and kill it. Meanwhile, Sam starts to develop frightening abilities that include death visions, visions of people dying before it actually happens. These visions are somehow connected to the demon who murdered his mother and its mysterious plans that seem to be all about Sam. When their father dies striking a deal with the very same devil that had killed his wife, the brothers, now alone and without their mentor, are determined to finish the crusade their father started. But disturbing revelations about Sam's part in the demon's apocalyptic plans are presented when John's dying last words to Dean are revealed.
15 | 44min | Drama, Fantasy, Horror | TV Series (2005– )</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/supernatural.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjA1MTkyNDI1N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDExMTQzNg@@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNGVkYTEwZjMtYmE4Yy00NWQ3LThiMWUtNzUxZTZlMDhkMzZhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDQ2MTMzODA@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Stranger Things </title>
<summary>Storyline
When a young boy disappears, his mother, a police chief, and his friends must confront terrifying forces in order to get him back.
</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/strangerthings.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTk3NTc2NTI0N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDA4MjcwNzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,704,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://images3.alphacoders.com/882/882548.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>South Park</title>
<summary>Storyline
Follows the misadventures of four irreverent grade-schoolers in the quiet, dysfunctional town of South Park, Colorado.
</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/southpark.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BOGE2YWUzMDItNTg2Ny00NTUzLTlmZGYtNWMyNzVjMjQ3MThkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BM2I1NTBjODMtYjIzYi00ZWIzLWJjNTktZGIzODhhZTEzODc3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyOTQ2MDgwNDg@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Goldbergs</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Before there were parenting blogs, trophies for showing up, and peanut allergies, there was a simpler time called the '80s. For geeky 11-year old Adam these were his wonder years and he faced them armed with a video camera to capture all the crazy.
22min | Comedy | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/thegoldbergs.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTA4ODUwODEzMzReQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDM0NjM3NjMy._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BYTRjYWY0MmMtYmFlOS00ZDJiLTgwYjUtMGE1ZDRiNDU3ODAxL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyODY0NzcxNw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>Taboo</title>
 <summary>Storyline
  Adventurer James Keziah Delaney returns to London during the War of 1812 to rebuild his late father's shipping empire. However, both the government and his biggest competitor want his inheritance at any cost - even murder. 
</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/taboo.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYyNTQwNzk0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDAyMDI2MDI@._V1_SY1000_SX666_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTRhOWUxMTQtYWQ5Zi00MTg2LWFjMmEtNDBiZDEwZTcxMjJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDg4MjkzNDk@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Grand Tour</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Follow Jeremy, Richard, and James, as they embark on an adventure across the globe. Driving new and exciting automobiles from manufacturers all over the world.
15 | 1h | Comedy, Talk-Show | TV Series (2016– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/thegrandtour.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTg4ZTYzY2UtMGZiNS00YTdmLThmM2MtODRlNWY1MWJkMTQyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjI4OTg2Njg@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjdmNzNmYjgtZjA4Ni00YTkzLWI5OGYtODkyYzU0MDg1ODA5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDEzMzgxNzY@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Last Man On Earth</title>
  <summary>Storyline
This is the story about the life and adventures of the last man on earth. Phil Miller was once just an average guy who loved his family and hated his job at the bank - now he's humanity's last hope. Will he ever find another person alive on the planet? Would hoping that she is a female be asking too much?
22min | Action, Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2015–2018)</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/thelastmanonearth.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BOTQ3NzM1MzQ0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNjAzNTQxODE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMmU1NDRhMDgtODQ3Mi00ZDQyLWI4MGItZDI2N2YxZjRlYmM0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTcxNjkwNzc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Big Bang Theory</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Leonard Hofstadter and Sheldon Cooper are both brilliant physicists working at Cal Tech in Pasadena, California. They are colleagues, best friends, and roommates, although in all capacities their relationship is always tested primarily by Sheldon's regimented, deeply eccentric, and non-conventional ways. They are also friends with their Cal Tech colleagues mechanical engineer Howard Wolowitz and astrophysicist Rajesh Koothrappali. The foursome spend their time working on their individual work projects, playing video games, watching science-fiction movies, or reading comic books. As they are self-professed nerds, all have little or no luck with women. When Penny, a pretty woman and an aspiring actress from Omaha, moves into the apartment across the hall from Leonard and Sheldon's, Leonard has another aspiration in life, namely to get Penny to be his girlfriend.
15 | 22min | Comedy, Romance | TV Series (2007– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/thebigbangtheory.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BY2FmZTY5YTktOWRlYy00NmIyLWE0ZmQtZDg2YjlmMzczZDZiXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjg4NzAyOTA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQ3NzM2MTc5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTA4NDQwMDI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Blacklist</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A highly articulate, erudite and intelligent businessman and mastermind, "Red" Reddington, has allegedly been on the "10 Most Wanted List" of various U.S. law enforcement agencies for over 20 years. The legend is that Red is as elusive as he is clever, controlling a labyrinth of creative enterprises, coupled with uncanny ability to gather and finesse information at the drop of a hat. On the first day at FBI for a new female profiler fresh out of Quantico, Red offers to bandy wits with the FBI. Red promises to deliver various criminals and plots previously unknown to any branch of law enforcement... and all Red requests in return is to choose his muse.
43min | Crime, Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/theblacklist.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMGYyZDFjOGMtNDE2Zi00ODg3LWJiZjktMWFiYjUwOTVmNjBkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjMxNzcwOTI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTQyNTQzNDEyNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODQ2NDM2NDE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Cool Kids</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Three friends at a retirement center have their comfortable existence rattled by a newcomer to the community.
22min | Comedy | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/thecoolkids.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjM2Njg2NjExOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzU5OTQwNjM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWUxOGNkNDItNjcyZi00MjQyLWFmODEtMDdjOTJhMjA1ZDE3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc5Mjg0NjU@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,962_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Crossing</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Refugees from a war-torn country 180 years in the future start showing up in the present to seek asylum in an American town. 
42min | Adventure, Drama, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2018– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/thecrossing.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjIxMjMxMTc1OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzg1Mjg1NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNzZhNDE3NjgtNzFmYS00Y2U5LThlMjMtMjAxZTVhNjU2ZmRmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzE5MTM1NTQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>The Defenders</title>
<summary>Storyline
"Marvel's The Defenders" follows Daredevil, Jessica Jones, Luke Cage and Iron Fist. A quartet of singular heroes with one common goal - to save New York City. This is the story of four solitary figures, burdened with their own personal challenges, who realize they just might be stronger when teamed together.
15 | 50min | Action, Adventure, Crime | TV Mini-Series (2017– )</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/thedefenders.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWU4NmY3MTMtMTBmMi00NjFjLTkwMmItYWZhZWUwNDg5M2ExXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDUyOTg3Njg@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNWI1N2Y4NzctMDczYS00NWM4LTk1NDktMmQxM2QwYTBhNjFkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzg1MDE5MTk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Deuce</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Based in 1970s New York, this show gives a raw and gritty portayal of the prostitution business that was so publicly executed at that time. As a result of police crack-down, the characters are forced to venture towards relatively safer and more discrete forms of the same work.
18 | 1h | Drama | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/thedeuce.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmYyMjUwMjQtZmE4NC00NmEwLWE1MTAtMDE3OGE4ZmY1MzNlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjU2ODM5MjU@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjc3MjRkMTMtZDZkZC00NjAzLWFlY2ItMzE1OTRiOWNlZGI1XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjc4MTAzOTM@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Flash</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Barry Allen is a Central City police forensic scientist with a reasonably happy life, despite the childhood trauma of a mysterious red and yellow lightning killing his mother and framing his father. All that changes when a massive particle accelerator accident leads to Barry being struck by lightning in his lab. Coming out of coma nine months later, Barry and his new friends at S.T.A.R labs find that he now has the ability to move at superhuman speed. Furthermore, Barry learns that he is but one of many affected by that event, most of whom are using their powers for evil. Determined to make a difference, Barry dedicates his life to fighting such threats, as The Flash. While he gains allies he never expected, there are also secret forces determined to aid and manipulate him for their own agenda.
12 | 43min | Action, Adventure, Drama | TV Series (2014– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/theflash.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTQzNmEwZTMtZGNkNC00YjQ5LThhYzMtZTBhNzUzODI5ZjRjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjM5NzU3OTM@._V1_SY1000_SX800_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjJjODg5ODMtNjQxNi00MWQ4LTg4Y2ItMjg5ZjAxYmQ0NmVlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjY2MjIyMDc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Gifted</title>
  <summary>Storyline
In a world where mutated humans are treated with distrust and fear, an institute for mutants battles to achieve peaceful co-existence with humanity.
43min | Action , Drama , Fantasy | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/thegifted.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzY5NTI0ODg5MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTM0NjM5MjI@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTYyMzc3NzM2NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTg0MDA3MjI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,947_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>The Punisher</title>
 <summary>Storyline
 After the murder of his family, Marine veteran Frank Castle becomes the vigilante known as "The Punisher," with only one goal in mind: to avenge them.
 </summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/punisher.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTExODIwOTUxNzFeQTJeQWpwZ15BbWU4MDE5MDA0MTcz._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGM1ZTEyZGEtYjc0NS00MDY5LTg5ODAtZTc1ZjBjN2MxOWRmXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDg4MjkzNDk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
<title>The Simpsons </title>
<summary>Storyline
The satiric adventures of a working-class family in the misfit city of Springfield.
</summary>
<link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/thesimpsons.xml</link>
<thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYjFkMTlkYWUtZWFhNy00M2FmLThiOTYtYTRiYjVlZWYxNmJkXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTAyODkwOQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
<fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODgyMGFhNjUtYzBmYi00MTg4LTllYzYtM2FmZjY5YWZhMWU0XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjMxOTcxOTI@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The 100</title>
  <summary>Storyline
The series is set 97 years after a devastating nuclear war wiped out almost all life on Earth. The only known survivors are the residents of twelve space stations in Earth's orbit prior to the war. The space stations banded together to form a single massive station named "The Ark", wenis galore about 2,400 people live. Resources are scarce and all crimes no matter their nature or severity are punishable by death ("floating") unless the perpetrator is under 18 years of age. After the Ark's life support systems are found to be critically failing, one hundred juvenile prisoners are declared "expendable" and sent to the surface in a last ditch attempt to determine if Earth is habitable again. The teens arrive on a beautiful planet they've only seen from space. Confronting the dangers of this rugged new world, they struggle to form a tentative community. However they discover that not all humanity was wiped out. There are people on Earth who survived the war, called "grounders" by the 100. The Ark consists of the space stations previously representing the nations of the UK, USA, Australia, Canada, China, Japan, India, Russia, Venezuela, France, Brazil, and Uganda.
  15 | 43min | Drama, Mystery, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2014– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/the100.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNDFlMDgyNTgtZGExMC00Njk0LWE1YjYtMDdlNGYzNGY1YzllL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTIxNjM3NzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMGRhNDIwNGQtODAwNy00YmJlLWExNWUtYWIwNWI0OWI5OTAxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzAwMzk3NjU@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,888_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Americans</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A pair of deep-cover Soviet spies masquerades as a typical DC couple whose children, neighbors, coworkers & friends are completely unaware of their activities. At home, they're the stereotypical parents of stereotypical kids; at work, they pose as travel agents; but at night, they weave a web of confidants, lovers, dupes, and historical figures from the Reagan-era Cold War. The startlingly realistic plot twists force the viewer to consider the real cost of an undeclared war, what it takes to protect one's beliefs, if it's worth it, and if it actually worked for either side.
12 | 44min | Crime, Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/theamericans.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjExMjk5NjI2NV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTU3MzU4NDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjI3NDU0ODUxMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzc3MjM2MTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1333,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Last Ship</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Naval Destroyer Nathan James is sent on what they're told is a research mission in the Arctic. Accompanying them is scientist, Rachel Scott. After a few months in the Arctic while Scott is on the ice doing research, some men attack them. They get back to the ship and the Commander, Tom Chandler asks the doctor what's going on. She says that a deadly disease broke out a few months ago. At first, they thought it was contained but they had no cure. They felt that the cure was in the Arctic which why she's here. But she has since received word that it has now spread to most of the globe. Chandler tries to call the President but learns the President and Vice President are dead and the US government might not have long to survive. The current President tells him that the Nathan James was not in the hot zone so he and his crew are OK. But now it's up to them to safeguard Scott because she holds the key to the planet's survival. But there are those who want the cure too and they will do whatever they have to, to get it. So they keep going and trying to find supplies and what they need so Scott can make the cure.
  15 | 1h | Action, Drama, Sci-Fi | TV Series (2014– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/thelastship.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMWY0MmUyNTAtMzZkMi00NmZkLTlkOGMtMDlhYjUyNWJmMjcxXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTUwNjUzODc@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMDQ5NTQ4ZGQtY2ZjNS00ZDQ4LWFlYTUtOWFlMmNiODNiYWEwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTk4OTQ0NDk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Last Kingdom</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  The year is 872, and many of the separate kingdoms of what we now know as England have fallen to the invading Danes, leaving the great kingdom of Wessex standing alone and defiant under the command of King Alfred.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/thelastkingdom.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjE1MzYzNjk3OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMzk0MzYwNzE@._V1_SX667_CR0,0,667,999_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWExM2FmZDctZjFkOC00MWI0LTgyZjYtMGNhMjE5NzQzMzUyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMzk2OTIwMjA@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,1501,1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>True Detective</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Seasonal anthology series in which police investigations unearth the personal and professional secrets of those involved, both within and outside the law.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/truedetective.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTY0ODc2NTc0NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDcyNTAwNzM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BZGM2MzEzNTQtMGY1Ni00ODA2LThlNzItYjU2N2I5Mjg4MWYyXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNzEyNjU3MDQ@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Office</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  A mockumentary on a group of typical office workers, where the workday consists of ego clashes, inappropriate behavior, and tedium.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/theoffice.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTgzNjAzMDE0NF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTEyMzM3OA@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,736,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://i.ytimg.com/vi/8GxqvnQyaxs/maxresdefault.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Originals</title>
  <summary>Storyline
A spin-off from The Vampire Diaries and set in New Orleans, The Originals centers on the Mikaelson siblings, otherwise known as the world's original vampires: Klaus (Joseph Morgan), Elijah (Daniel Gillies), and Rebekah (Claire Holt). Now Klaus must take down his protégé, Marcel (Charles Michael Davis), who is now in charge of New Orleans, in order to re-take his city, as he originally built New Orleans. Klaus departed from the city after being chased down by his father Mikael, while it was being constructed and Marcel took charge. As Klaus has returned after many years, his ego has provoked him to become the king of the city. "Every King needs an heir" says Klaus, accepting the unborn child. The child is a first to be born to a hybrid (part vampire, part werewolf) and a werewolf (Hayley).
15 | 45min | Drama, Fantasy, Horror | TV Series (2013– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/theoriginals.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMzM0NDI4Mjc5OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjgxNzEzNTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTZlZmNjYzgtMWI4NC00MmJiLWJlM2MtMmNhYmQ1ODg1MjQ2L2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjc0NjA1NjU@._V1_SX1777_CR0,0,1777,996_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Walking Dead</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Sheriff Deputy Rick Grimes gets shot and falls into a coma. When awoken he finds himself in a Zombie Apocalypse. Not knowing what to do he sets out to find his family, after he's done that he gets connected to a group to become the leader. He takes charge and tries to help this group of people survive, find a place to live, and get them food. This show is all about survival, the risks, and the things you'll have to do to survive.
18 | 44min | Drama, Horror, Thriller | TV Series (2010– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/thewalkingdead.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BZTA3OGU2Y2EtYWIxNy00ZThmLWJhNjYtMmU5NDk4ZWI3Yzc3XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDI4MzQ0MzQ@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNjhjN2RjOTgtMGZiNi00NDQ3LWFmOGYtYmJjNDFhNjBkM2JjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjA4MDAzNTg@._V1_SY1000_SX1000_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Wire</title>
   <summary>Storyline
  Set in Baltimore, this show centers around the city's inner-city drug scene. It starts as mid-level drug dealer, D'Angelo Barksdale beats a murder rap.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/thewire.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNjc1NzYwODEyMV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNTcxMzU1MQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,735,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNWZiYzA5N2YtY2UxYS00NzkzLWI3MmUtNDE0NTFjOGFiY2QwXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTgyNDM1OTU@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The West Wing </title>
   <summary>Storyline
   Presidential advisers get their personal lives hopelessly tangled up with professional duties as they try to conduct the business of running a country. Fictional Democratic President Josiah "Jed" Bartlet suffers no fools, and that policy alienates many. He and his dedicated staffers struggle to balance the needs of the country with the political realities of Washington, D.C., working through two presidential terms that include countless scandals, threats and political scuffles, as well as the race to succeed Bartlet as the leader of the free world.
   </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/thewestwing.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BODEwZDFlMGMtNWU2NS00NDU5LWI3MjgtNjdkM2I0MGFjMWNjXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNTA4NzY1MzY@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,732,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjJkMzQ2ODQtNDBhZi00NDllLTkyZTgtZTc2ZDY4OWM5MmM4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMjk3NTUyOTc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Umbrella Academy </title>
   <summary>Storyline
   On the same day in October 1989, forty-three infants are inexplicably born to random, unconnected women who showed no signs of pregnancy the day before. Seven are adopted by Sir Reginald Hargreeves, a billionaire industrialist, who creates The Umbrella Academy and prepares his "children" to save the world. But not everything went according to plan. In their teenage years, the family fractured and the team disbanded. Now, the six surviving thirty-something members reunite upon the news of Hargreeves' passing. Luther, Diego, Allison, Klaus, Vanya and Number Five work together to solve a mystery surrounding their father's death. But the estranged family once again begins to come apart due to their divergent personalities and abilities, not to mention the imminent threat of a global apocalypse.
   </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/theumbrellaacademy.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTFhOTk1NTgtYWM1ZS00NWI1LTgzYzAtYmE5MjZiMDE0NzlhXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMTkxNjUyNQ@@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,675,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BYWZmNGQ3YTYtZmZlYi00OWM3LWJiODYtNzQ5NDhhOWYwY2U5XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjU2MDMzMjk@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The X Files </title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Two F.B.I. Agents, Fox Mulder the believer and Dana Scully the skeptic, investigate the strange and unexplained, while hidden forces work to impede their efforts.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/thexfiles.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNzE4Njg5ODk0OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwOTU0MzAyNDM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://www.tvinsider.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/XGuys-1014x570.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>The Twilight Zone</title>
  <summary>Storyline
   Ordinary people find themselves in extraordinarily astounding situations, which they each try to solve in a remarkable manner.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/thetwilightzone.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMjAwMTQ1MjE3N15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTYwOTA5OTg4._V1._CR10,9,236,390_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BN2QxM2RhNjMtNWQ5MS00OTUxLTlkYzItZTJhOWIxNzNiZmYzXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyMDIyODA5Nw@@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Vikings</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  Vikings transports us to the brutal and mysterious world of Ragnar Lothbrok, a Viking warrior and farmer who yearns to explore - and raid - the distant shores across the ocean.
  </summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows/vikings.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDYyNzk1NzYwOF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTQ0Nzc4MzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,738,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkyMjgwODk4OV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNTY2MTUyNTE@._V1_SX1500_CR0,0,1500,999_AL_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>Z Nation</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Three years after the zombie virus has gutted the country, a team of everyday heroes must transport the only known survivor of the plague from New York to California, where the last functioning viral lab waits for his blood.
18 | 44min | Action, Comedy, Drama | TV Series (2014– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/znation.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjM5MjIzMTkyN15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMjE1OTE3MzI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,666,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODRlYTQ0YmItOGI2YS00YTZjLTg4ZDItNGU5MWU1ZDVjMTgxL2ltYWdlL2ltYWdlXkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNDIzMzcwNjc@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>12 Monkeys</title>
  <summary>Storyline
  In the year 2043, scavenger James Cole (Aaron Stanford) has been recruited by a team of "Project Splinter" scientists led by physicist Katarina Jones (Barbara Sukowa), to travel back in time to the year 2015, and stop the release of a deadly virus by the enigmatic organization known as the "Army of the 12 Monkeys". In Cole's original time-line, the virus caused a plague that resulted in the death of seven billion humans in the year 2017, and its on-going mutations will mean the eventual end of the human race. In the 2015 time-line, Cole will meet and enlist the help of brilliant virologist Dr. Cassandra "Cassie" Railly (Amanda Schull); the two are brought together because a recording mentioning Cole, that Cassie made after the viral outbreak, is uncovered by Jones in the future time-line, prompting her to select Cole for the mission. Cole will also encounter a seemingly unstable math genius named Jennifer Goines (Emily Hampshire), whose father Cole has been tasked to kill, Cassie's ex-boyfriend Aaron Marker (Noah Bean), and the dangerous high-ranking members of the Army of the 12 Monkeys, "Pallid Man" (Tom Noonan) and Olivia (Alisen Down). In the future time-line, Cole will also have to deal with his best friend José Ramse (Kirk Acevedo), and a man named Theodore Deacon (Todd Stashwick), who leads a brutal pack of scavengers from which Cole and Ramse fled. Meanwhile, Cole and Cassie will try to unveil the identity and whereabouts of the mysterious leader of the Army of the 12 Monkeys, who is only known as "The Witness", and is always one step ahead of them.
  42min | Adventure, Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2015– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/12monkeys.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTkwOTcxNzMzOV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwODYxNjg0ODE@._V1_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BMTc1NTk2MDg1MV5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMDY1MTc0MzE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>

<dir>
  <title>13 Reasons Why</title>
  <summary>Storyline
Thirteen Reasons Why, based on the best-selling books by Jay Asher, follows teenager Clay Jensen (Dylan Minnette) as he returns home from school to find a mysterious box with his name on it lying on his porch. Inside he discovers a group of cassette tapes recorded by Hannah Baker (Katherine Langford) -his classmate and crush-who tragically committed suicide two weeks earlier. On tape, Hannah unfolds an emotional audio diary, detailing the thirteen reasons why she decided to end her life. Through Hannah and Clay's dual narratives, Thirteen Reasons Why weaves an intricate and heartrending story of confusion and desperation that will deeply affect viewers.
15 | 1h | Drama, Mystery | TV Series (2017– )</summary>
  <link>http://venomrepo.xyz/paul/1clickshows2/1clickshows3/13reasonswhy.xml</link>
  <thumbnail>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNDgwNDU2MjgwMl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTE2NzQ0NTM@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,674,1000_AL_.jpg</thumbnail>
  <fanart>https://m.media-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNmE0ZTA1NTUtZDBjNy00M2JmLThjODYtMzAwYmEyNDNiNmU4XkEyXkFqcGdeQXVyNjgzNTU5ODE@._V1_.jpg</fanart>
</dir>





